<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="37561" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./2020bb.zip</path>
		<name>2020 Super Baseball</name>
		<desc>In the year 2020, baseball finally evolved. There is no longer conventional professional baseball in 2020. Baseball designed by the Super Baseball Association has been very popular and is the best sport.

However, the truth is that the association has used a colossal sum of money to promote Super Baseball as show business. They have manipulated each player's ability using the control computer to secretly decide victory or defeat in every game. The players who knew this removed the connecting parts of the computer to play their own game of baseball. Finally, a fair game is going to be played at Cyber Egg Stadium.

In 2020 Super Baseball is a fast-paced game with new rules, where you can select 1 of 12 individual men, women, or robot players. During play, you can make your team stronger with prizes earned from amazing catches.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/2020bb.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/2020bb.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/2020bb.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pallas</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37563" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./alpham2.zip</path>
		<name>Alpha Mission II</name>
		<desc>The lunar nightmare of a bloody 200-year space war was thought to be over in the "original" ALPHA MISSION. But now with the advent of more technically sophisticated weapons, the evil "Fulvar" and his "Seven Star Alliance" have returned to destroy all planets that stand in their way of the ultimate target... Earth! Now in the year of 2525! Your mission as pilot of the new SYD-FX fighter is to use every weapon at your disposal to rid the galaxy once and for all of the evil that now dominates and threatens Earth. So suit up, hold your breath, and stand ready for unbelievable graphics and stereo sound that'll suck you into the far reaches of deep, dark inner space. Be prepared... you may never come back!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/alpham2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/alpham2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/alpham2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13927" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./androdun.zip</path>
		<name>Andro Dunos</name>
		<desc>The invasion of an unknown life source is getting worse. Nobody knows if the defensive line or the heart of the enemy base is ruined first. With the people's hope, the most advanced fighter will be dispatched into multi-scrolling space.

Fight your way through seven stages in this horizontal-scrolling game, and defeat a boss at the end of each one. You start the game with four main weapons, which you can switch from with the click of a button. Some of these weapons are more powerful than others. You can also fire off a charged shot if your main weapon level is two or greater, simply by holding down the fire button for about two seconds. Using charged shots can do more damage to an enemy ship. If you happen to die, you will lose one power level from all four weapons. If all your lives are lost and are forced to continue, you will start again with your main weapon on the second power level and all three sub-weapons on the first power level.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/androdun.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/androdun.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/androdun.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920717T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37564" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./aodk.zip</path>
		<name>Aggressors of Dark Kombat</name>
		<desc>Aggressors of Dark Kombat is another one-on-one street fighting beat 'em up from the Neo-Geo's seemingly endless library of fighters.

It pits 8 fighters of different styles and strengths against each other in a tournament to see who's the toughest mofo on the streets of Tokyo. Your objective as usual is to deplete your opponent's health bar within the time limit by using your basic attacks and special moves (triggered by specific controller motions) while avoiding his moves and attacks.

Unique to Aggressors of Dark Kombat is the combination of traditional side-scrolling beat 'em up elements, meaning characters can freely move in an isometric space instead of being restricted to a single plane of movement. Weapons and throw-able items are usually thrown into the arena by the crowds and you can pick them up and wield them for added damage. Additionally, matches are 1-round only affairs, with an extended multi-layered health bar that allows for longer rounds than usual.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/aodk.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/aodk.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/aodk.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19940826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37565" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./aof.zip</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting</name>
		<desc>The storyline of Art of Fighting takes place in 1978. Ryo Sakazaki and Robert Garcia set out to find Ryo's sister, Yuri, who was kidnapped by Mr. Big. Mr. Big took Yuri to entice Takuma Sakazaki, Ryo's father and originator of Kyokugen Karate, and also because Ryo refused to work for Big. After Ryo &amp; Robert defeat Mr. Big, they face the enigmatic Mr. Karate. Art of Fighting's story ends with a cliff-hanger; Yuri is about to disclose the true identity of Mr. Karate as their father Takuma.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/aof.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/aof.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/aof.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19921211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37566" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./aof2.zip</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting 2</name>
		<desc>In this sequel to the original Art of Fighting, and prequel to the original Fatal Fury, we learn that Mr. Karate, the final boss of the original game, behind the mask, is really Takuma Sakazaki, Ryo and Yuri's father, that Takuma was being used by Geese Howard for his own evil intentions, and that Mr. Big was the one who had originally kidnapped Yuri.

Many of the problems that existed in the first game have been fixed in this installment (it is easier to execute special moves, you no longer have only Ryo or Robert to choose from in 1 player mode, etc.).

The entire cast from the first Art of Fighting is here (with the exceptions of Todo and Mr. Karate), along with a few new characters: Takuma Sakazaki, Ryo and Yuri's father; Yuri Sakazaki, Takuma's daughter and Ryo's sister; Eiji Kisaragi, a sworn enemy of the Sakazakis; Temjin, a Mongolian trucker; and a younger version of Geese Howard, whom you face as the last boss if you beat the game without losing a round.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/aof2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/aof2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/aof2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="40019" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./aof3.zip</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting 3 - The Path of the Warrior</name>
		<desc>Art of Fighting 3 featured a new cast of characters with the exception of Ryo and Robert. Yuri Sakazaki is seen in the game, but only as a side character in Ryo and Robert's story mode.
The story switched focus from the Sakazakis to Robert Garcia. Garcia disappears to search for an old childhood friend, Freia Lawrence, and he tracks her to GlassHill, Mexico. Freia is wanted by the game's main antagonist, Wyler, to complete a powerful elixir that was created by his and Freia's fathers. The drug affects users in a similar manner as the potion in The Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde.
One of the game's characters, Kasumi Todoh, became a part of The King of Fighters cast. This game is the only one in the series to have a CD Drama Arranged Soundtrack.[2]
It was re-released for the Wii's Virtual Console in North America on 21 March 2013 at a cost of 900 Wii Points.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/aof3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/aof3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/aof3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37568" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./bangbead.zip</path>
		<name>Bang Bead</name>
		<desc>Bang Bead, known in Japan as Bang Beads, is a 2001 ball-and-paddle game developed and published by Visco exclusively for the arcade cabinet known as the SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware. It combines the genres of the Magnavox Odyssey Tennis game, Atari's Pong and Breakout arcades, and Nintendo's Spitball Sparky of the Game &amp; Watch series. You can select from 9 characters and play against another player or the computer. Knock out the stars behind the other player then get the bouncing ball through to win the round.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/bangbead.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/bangbead.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/bangbead.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37569" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./bjourney.zip</path>
		<name>Blue's Journey</name>
		<desc>The planet of Raguy was once beautiful and peaceful, but all hell broke loose when it was invaded by the Daruma tribe. The pollution started to spread through the city. Blue was summoned to get rid of the Daruma tribe, and save Raguy from the Daruma Empire that has turned the inhabitants into slaves.

You control Blue, who only has one weapon to deal with the Darumas. You can use his leaf to whip enemies upside-down, and hurl these enemies at others. Along the way, you can get flowers for use at the shop to buy items that will help you along the way. These items include flower honey (increases stamina), swim fins (easier swimming), light safe (protects all your items), spikes, and ocarinas. Later in the game, you can also get the shopkeeper to sing you a song. This helps you break curses that are placed on you by a witch.You will also interact with other characters along the way that can also help you if you tell the truth.

You exit each stage by jumping on a huge plant. The higher up you are on this plant, the more points you are awarded. Every two or so stages, you have to defeat a boss before a guy in a devil suit offers you something. You can refuse or accept the other. If you accept the offer, you will have to pull one of four strings that will give you a life ball, more stamina, 30 flowers, cocoons, or five flowers.

You are on a time limit. If you run out of time, a black creature appears out of nowhere, and starts firing "bird" missiles at you.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/bjourney.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/bjourney.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/bjourney.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13893" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./blazstar.zip</path>
		<name>Blazing Star</name>
		<desc>The unofficial sequel to Pulstar, Blazing Star is again a horizontal-scrolling shoot-'em-up. One or two players proceed along levels, each with a boss enemy at the end, trying to redeem the humankind. There are six ships to choose from, each with its own pilot (four of them females), weapons and characteristics of movement. Each ship has its own types of shots, but also a standard shot, charged shot (more powerful) and split shot (a charged shot can be parted into more bullets, lowering the power of each bullet while widening the fire range).</desc>
		<image>./boxart/blazstar.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/blazstar.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/blazstar.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13877" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./breakers.zip</path>
		<name>Breakers</name>
		<desc>In Breakers, choose one of eight fighters who have their own moves and special attacks. There are eight stages in the game, and each stage has two battles. The object of each battle is to drain your opponent's energy in order to win the battle. If there is a draw, a third battle takes place. If the time limit expires, the player with the less energy loses the battle. Once you have completed all eight stages, you will face a opponent that is much tougher than previous ones. Different endings and in-game dialog are viewed depending on the character that you select.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/breakers.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/breakers.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/breakers.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19961217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37570" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./breakrev.zip</path>
		<name>Breakers Revenge</name>
		<desc>8 initially selectable characters face off to become the Tae Kwon Do master! After defeating the absolutely WACKY Master Taekuk, he becomes selectable as well to face off against end boss Karate Kenji.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/breakrev.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/breakrev.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/breakrev.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37571" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./bstars.zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars Professional</name>
		<desc>Baseball Stars Professional is the follow-up to Baseball Stars for the Nintendo Entertainment System, and features comic-style graphics. Choose from a variety of teams that include Celestial Planets, Heavenly Bodies, Shadow Demons, Battle Knights, Fabulous Superstars, and many others. Then select the field where the game is to be held: The SNK stadium or the SNK dome. Each field has the same dimensions, but their capacity varies. The game is played the same way as normal baseball. Features a VS. mode in which two players can play against each other.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/bstars.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/bstars.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/bstars.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13951" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./bstars2.zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars 2</name>
		<desc>This follow up to Baseball Stars Professional features a fast-paced arcade style baseball with six fictitious teams, each with their own strengths and weaknesses.  There are two difficulties of play: Beginner, which automatically fields the ball for the player while Exciting has the player do the field manually.  Additionally, there are two main modes of play where in the single player mode the player will compete in a fifteen-team tournament or go head-to-head against a friend in a multiplayer mode.

The standard rules of baseball still apply, but it adds power-ups that the player can pick up and use during the game, such as the ability for their pitcher to throw faster or their batter to hit better. They can also substitute a player during the game, but are limited to three substitutions per game. The game is shown through 2D graphics with comic-style cutscenes to illustrate the action, such as dramatic catches and home runs that will pop-up during the game.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/bstars2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/bstars2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/bstars2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37572" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./burningf.zip</path>
		<name>Burning Fight</name>
		<desc>The Castella family from the Metro City started ruining the peaceful city of Osaka with the violent Japanese group, "Heiwa-gumi". To stop the fight, Metro police detectives dispatched two dangerous characters, Duke and Billy, to Japan. With the support of the famous Japanese detective Ryu, they decided to rush into the enemy's fortress. Ruthless violence in the neon lights of Osaka. Will there be an end to this war?

Burning Fight is a side-scrolling street-fighting game similar to Final Fight. As Duke, Billy, or Ryu, you must fight your way through the various locations in Osaka. At the start of the game, you can only use your fists to deal with gangs, but by by breaking things like phone booths and street signs along the way, you can get new weapons and more health. At the end of each location, you will have to defeat a boss in order to continue the mission.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/burningf.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/burningf.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/burningf.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13924" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./crsword.zip</path>
		<name>Crossed Swords</name>
		<desc>As a knight, you must travel the countryside fighting monsters and bandits using your sword and shield. When you enter combat the view changes to a pseudo 1st-person perspective where the body of your knight is outlined so that you can see the creatures that you are fighting. When enemies have been defeated, they drop money and power-ups. There are seven chapters in the game, and each chapter (except one) starts with you entering a merchant's shop and buying weapons using the money that you have collected so far. There are also alternate paths which take you to different parts of the game. At the start of the game, you may choose a chapter (from one to three only) you want to start at.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/crsword.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/crsword.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/crsword.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13938" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ctomaday.zip</path>
		<name>Captain Tomaday</name>
		<desc>A comical vertically scrolling shoot'em up starring a mutated tomato who punches the enemy and can transform to other weird characters.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ctomaday.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ctomaday.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ctomaday.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13931" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./cyberlip.zip</path>
		<name>Cyber-Lip</name>
		<desc>Cyber-Lip is a 1-2 player side-scrolling game where you must fight your way through several areas, and defeat a boss at the end of each one. Along the way, you can pick up a variety of weapons along the way, and use them against the invaders. By destroying certain enemies, you receive a "core bot", which is a ring that surrounds you, and when this touches the invaders, they are destroyed. Time is against you. When it expires, you lose a life.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/cyberlip.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/cyberlip.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/cyberlip.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37573" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./doubledr.zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>Released around the same time as the film of the same name and loosely based on its story, this installment in the Double Dragon series also moves away from the traditional roam-the-streets-fighting to a pure one-on-one fighter. There are ten characters to choose from, including Billy and Jimmy and the game has colorful interactive backgrounds, screen zooming, over-the-top special moves and with the inclusion of double jumps, combos, charges for the losing player and counter hits, there is plenty of room for advanced fighting strategies.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/doubledr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/doubledr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/doubledr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="41092" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./eightman.zip</path>
		<name>Eight Man</name>
		<desc>Eightman (c) 1991 SNK [Shin Nihon Kikaku].  A side-scrolling beat'em up / platform game.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS Hardware Game ID : [Model NGM-025]  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  [SNK MVS Neo</desc>
		<image>./boxart/eightman.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/eightman.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/eightman.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK / Pallas</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37575" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fatfursp.zip</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury Special</name>
		<desc>Fatal Fury Special is an improved version of SNK's 2D one-on-one fighter Fatal Fury 2. It's a conversion of the 1993 arcade game of the same name. The objective is still to win the tournament by defeating all other fighters including end boss Wolfgang Krauser. Fatal Fury Special features a fairly large selection of fighters. A new Count Down mode (defeat as many opponents as possible in 3 minutes).Extra color schemes for every character.New &amp; improved background graphics.Dolby Surround Sound support.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fatfursp.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fatfursp.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fatfursp.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37576" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fatfury1.zip</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury - King of Fighters</name>
		<desc>Southtown City plays host to the King of Fighters Tournament. Andy &amp; Terry Bogard take part in the tournament cause winning the tournament is the only way they can defeat Geese Howard. Geese Howard controls Southtown City and killed their father several years ago. Also taking part is Joe Higashi, a Japanese kickboxer. Select either Joe, Andy or Terry, visit several locations in Southtown City and win that tournament!

Fatal Fury is a 2D fighter and is the first game in a series of one-on-one fighting games by SNK. It's a conversion of the original Fatal Fury arcade game. This first game does not yet feature the series' trademark pseudo 3D mode (which allows you to move between the foreground &amp; background while fighting). Includes a two-player vs. mode.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fatfury1.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fatfury1.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fatfury1.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37577" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fatfury2.zip</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury 2</name>
		<desc>Again, the Lone Wolves return!

Geese Howard may have been defeated, but that doesn't mean all is peaceful. A new opponent, Wolfgang Krauser, has come forth to begin a new Fatal Fury tournament. The Lone Wolves return, with new faces amongst them. Only one can be declared the winner though.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fatfury2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fatfury2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fatfury2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37578" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fatfury3.zip</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury 3 - Road to the Final Victory</name>
		<desc>An adaptation of the Neo-Geo fighting game.  2-D scrolling one-on-one fighter with pseudo-3D aspects (that allows for players to "escape" holds, throws, and other attacks.)  Part of the incestuously-popular SNK fighting game pantheon...
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fatfury3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fatfury3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fatfury3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13966" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fbfrenzy.zip</path>
		<name>Football Frenzy</name>
		<desc>You'll never play another football game again, after you play Football Frenzy! Football Frenzy, with on-going play-by-play announcing, is hard-hitting action at its best! You will hear, in full stereo, every bone-crushing tackle and helmet-to-helmet, metal-on-metal hit. The piercing grunts and groans of players sacrificing their bodies for the team puts you right on the field with them! The camera zooms give you the most dazzling close-ups ever seen. So, bring your pads and helmet! Tournament mode, cinematic displays and over 10 teams to choose from make this football package complete. Play against the computer or a friend in this 46-MEG bone-jarring gridiron great... Football Frenzy!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fbfrenzy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fbfrenzy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fbfrenzy.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37579" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fightfev.zip</path>
		<name>Fight Fever</name>
		<desc>There are 8 characters to select from and two boss characters (the first boss character is only playable in two player mode). The object of the game is to win two matches out of three. Each character has a set of moves in addition to two basic punches and kicks. Each character also has a super move called a "Danger Move", which are similar to the Desperation Moves from Fatal Fury 2. Players also have the ability to taunt others, but unlike games such as Art of Fighting, this has no effect and would actually leave the player open to attacks.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fightfev.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fightfev.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fightfev.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Viccom</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13917" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./flipshot.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Flip Shot</name>
		<desc>Battle Flip Shot is an arcade game that mixes elements of Pong with Japanese character design.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/flipshot.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/flipshot.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/flipshot.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37580" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./galaxyfg.zip</path>
		<name>Galaxy Fight</name>
		<desc>People have prayed to the gods, but the devil descends from the sky. Your mission is to defeat Felden Kryse, ruler of the underworld. The fantastic challenge ferociously unfolds on eight different planets. Screen image changes on-the-fly to zoom in and out based on how the battle unfolds. Use Dash to your utmost advantage, and speed through the field of infinity.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/galaxyfg.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/galaxyfg.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/galaxyfg.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13945" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ganryu.zip</path>
		<name>Ganryu</name>
		<desc>One month has passed since Musashi defeated his sworn enemy, Kojiro. Musashi was on the way to Kyoto, where his beloved Otsu was waiting for him. Around this time, many abductions had occurred by a mysterious group of ninjas, and Otsu was one of the missing. What is the true purpose of these ninjas? The time to fight has come again for Musashi!!

You must guide Musashi or his sister, Suzame, around several locations defeating a horde of ninjas with only a sword. Weapon power-ups and life bonuses can be collected along the way. You can jump high and use your grappling hook to attach to and climb some ceilings, as well as attaching yourself to faraway objects. At the end of each location, you must defeat a guardian in order to continue the game. Cut-scenes are viewed between locations.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ganryu.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ganryu.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ganryu.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37581" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./garou.zip</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury: Mark of the Wolves</name>
		<desc>It's been several years since Geese Howard was defeated in a battle with Terry Bogard, a young man looking to avenge his father. Rather than looking to be saved from death after falling off his office balcony, Geese instead decided to die, and left behind his young son, Rock. Terry took Rock in and became like a big brother to him, raising the boy throughout his life.

Now Rock is a teenager, and Terry is a man in his 30s, and both are about to come together in a new clash...new faces and old come together for the greatest battle yet!
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/garou.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/garou.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/garou.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20000225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37582" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ghostlop.zip</path>
		<name>Ghostlop</name>
		<desc>Ghost Lop is an excellent Ghostbusters themed puzzle game by Data East from 1996. It combines the fast action of an Arkanoid style game, with the quick thinking of a Bust-A-Move type game. The game was re-considered for release in 2001, but SNK's untimely demise later that same year may have ended that possibility. Data East was best known for its' Chain Reaction / Magical Drop series of puzzle games, and even later included the Ghostlop characters in one of the later releases for modern home game systems.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ghostlop.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ghostlop.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ghostlop.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13906" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./goalx3.zip</path>
		<name>Goal! Goal! Goal!</name>
		<desc>A soccer game with all the right ingredients, skill, flair, passion, and of course, GOALS! With 28 national teams to choose from, compete in a tournament to become the best soccer nation in the world. Get past the opening group stage and go on to a round-robin elimination stage where failure is not an option. To help you on your way, hold down the shoot button until the power bar fills up and you can do a POWERFUL SUPER SHOT!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/goalx3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/goalx3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/goalx3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="41498" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./gowcaizr.zip</path>
		<name>Voltage Fighter - Gowcaizer</name>
		<desc>An anime style fighting game that takes place in the Year 2010 in Tron City. In this city, there is a school for special students called the Belnar Institute. Isato Kaiza, the hero of the story, is a student at</desc>
		<image>./boxart/gowcaizr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/gowcaizr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/gowcaizr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Technos Japan</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37584" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./gpilots.zip</path>
		<name>Ghost Pilots</name>
		<desc>Ghost Pilots is an overhead military plane shooter, in which you must shoot down fighter jets by either using bullets or bombs. Once you have killed enough fighter jets, you will have to defeat a boss fighter jet in order to continue. After some stages, you must select a route to continue your journey on. Power-ups can be collected that will increase your firepower, and stars can be obtained for extra points.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/gpilots.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/gpilots.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/gpilots.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shoot'em Up</developer>
		<publisher>Shoot'em Up</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37585" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./gururin.zip</path>
		<name>Gururin</name>
		<desc>Your goal is to make three people of the same color line up and disappear--but to do that, you won't flip the people around as they fall but rather rotate the entire pit once they've landed. Like clothes in a dryer, you've got to flip the whole playfield around and try to match up the midgets as they slide down to the bottom of the screen, reorganizing themselves as they go.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/gururin.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/gururin.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/gururin.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FACE</developer>
		<publisher>FACE</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="87607" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ironclad.zip</path>
		<name>Choutetsu Brikin'ger - Iron clad</name>
		<desc>Ironclad is a side scrolling shooter developed by Saurus in 1996. Ironclad was first shown in its native MVS cartridge format at the March 1996 ACME show in Orlando, Florida. I saw and played the game at the show. We always knew therefore that at the very least, one proto was available on the MVS format. Although the game saw release on the NEOGEO CD system, it was never officially released in either the MVS or HOME cartridge formats. Ironclad was the most sought after of all the CD-protos because of its appeal to shoot 'em up fans. This was most likely why it had coincidentally caused the largest number of false claims; more then any other proto cartridge! 13 years later, in November of 2009, SNK finally released the native ROM data for the game and as a result we finally got the game and can now enjoy it forever!</desc>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="41839" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./irrmaze.zip</path>
		<name>The Irritating Maze</name>
		<desc>The Irritating Maze (c) 1997 SNK.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0236  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels Screen ref</desc>
		<image>./boxart/irrmaze.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/irrmaze.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/irrmaze.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK / Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="41913" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./joyjoy.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzled</name>
		<desc>Two cute little kids need you to help rescue their villages. Their way is blocked by rows of blocks. Destroy the rows of blocks and help them reach the head God so their villages can be saved.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/joyjoy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/joyjoy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/joyjoy.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Fall</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37589" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kabukikl.zip</path>
		<name>Far East of Eden - Kabuki Klash</name>
		<desc>"Kabuki Klash" is a 2D fighting game that features characters from the famous Japanese role-playing series  Tengai Makyou, also known as Far East of Eden. The heroes of the three first Tengai Makyou games must participate in a tournament and find out who is the most skillful fighter in the magical land of Jipang (which is very similar to the medieval Japan). The characters include well-known Far East of Eden heroes such as Ziria, Manjimaru, Kabuki, Orochimaru, and others - a total of eight playable characters. During the fights, you can either punch, kick, or use special attacks, that require a precise usage of buttons and also deplete your magic gauge. There are random items (such as healing potions) thrown on the battle field while you are fighting, which you can pick up.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kabukikl.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kabukikl.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kabukikl.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19951123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37590" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./karnovr.zip</path>
		<name>Karnov's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Karnov's Revenge is a 2-D Street Fighter II clone from Data East. Choose one of 13 fighters from around the world to play as, each with their unique moves and special attacks. As usual, there are two rounds in each stage, and the object of each round is to drain your opponent's energy in order to win the battle. If there is a tie after two rounds, a third round is played. There is a time limit, and if this expires, the player with the less energy loses.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/karnovr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/karnovr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/karnovr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK of America</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13920" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kizuna.zip</path>
		<name>Kizuna Encounter Super Tag Battle</name>
		<desc>Fight Alone!
Competition or Team Battles. The Tage Battle of a Lifetime Begins!
Or Fight with a Friend!

Why Do You Fight?! For money? For glory? For...?!
The Fate of 10 of the World's Mightiest Warriors Rests on the Grand Ambitions of King Lion!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kizuna.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kizuna.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kizuna.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19961108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42023" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof2000.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2000</name>
		<desc>34 characters, plus the popular striker system, await to be selected to team up and defeat the mighty Zero and his incredible bladed coat!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof2000.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof2000.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof2000.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42024" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof2001.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2001</name>
		<desc>With the largest KOF lineup totaling at 40 characters, newcomers Eolith do a great job at delivering high quality fighting action along with one of the most difficult pairs of bosses in fighting game history!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof2001.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof2001.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof2001.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eolith Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Eolith / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42025" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof2002.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2002</name>
		<desc>Revived 3 on 3 battles and new MAX Activation System enable you to get more and more exciting showdowns.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof2002.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof2002.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof2002.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eolith Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Eolith / Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="41975" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof2003.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2003</name>
		<desc>The King of Fighters 2003 turned out to be the last game in the series released on the Neo-Geo console. Ports with 3D backgrounds were made for other systems. Tag-team gameplay was added and the game introduced lot of new characters.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof2003.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof2003.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof2003.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42027" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof94.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '94</name>
		<desc>24 selectable characters in fixed teams of three clash to defeat Rugal Bernstein.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof94.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof94.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof94.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42028" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof95.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '95</name>
		<desc>8 teams comprised of 3 characters each square off again to take out Rugal Bernstein.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof95.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof95.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof95.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42029" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof96.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '96</name>
		<desc>The 3rd chapter in this groundbreaking series brings 27 classic SNK characters together against Goenitz, the final boss.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof96.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof96.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof96.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42030" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof97.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '97</name>
		<desc>9 teams of 3 and 2 solo entries pump the number of selectable characters up to 29 in a battle to defeat the evil Orochi and those infected with his blood.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof97.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof97.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof97.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42031" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof98.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '98 - The Slugfest</name>
		<desc>A special edition of the KoF series taking place outside of the established storyline with a whopping 38 selectable KoF alumni.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof98.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof98.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof98.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42032" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof99.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '99 - Millennium Battle</name>
		<desc>Introducing the new 'striker' system! Each team is expanded to four characters, with a total of 30 selectable characters set on defeating Krizalid and his evil feather coat.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof99.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof99.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof99.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37597" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kotm.zip</path>
		<name>King of the Monsters</name>
		<desc>King of the Monsters is a two player (or one player vs. computer) fighting game, in which the players take control of two gargantuan monsters (like Godzillas) and battle it out in different city locations.

The city gets gradually destroyed as the two creatures fight it out. The players can also interact with the scenery by picking up boats and such, to use as weapons against the other player.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kotm.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kotm.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kotm.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37598" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kotm2.zip</path>
		<name>King of the Monsters 2 - The Next Thing</name>
		<desc>The object of King of the Monsters 2 is similar to its predecessor. Choose from three monsters which include a large lizard, a large robotic ape, and a huge mutant human. Then walk through each city, making sure to destroy everything in site, including planes, buildings, and other creatures. When smashed, some buildings reveal power-ups that make your character more powerful. At the end of each city, you go head-to-head with the boss creature. There are small stages in between where you fight a second monster for bonus points, or you fall from the sky and land underwater where you try to collect points and power-ups while falling.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kotm2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kotm2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kotm2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Takara</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42105" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./lastblad.zip</path>
		<name>The Last Blade</name>
		<desc>Japanese weapons-based fighter featuring beautiful artwork and sound. Twelve selectable characters and two end bosses.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/lastblad.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/lastblad.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/lastblad.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42106" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./lastbld2.zip</path>
		<name>The Last Blade 2</name>
		<desc>Much-acclaimed swordplay fighter with sixteen selectable characters and one end boss. Another SNK triumph!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/lastbld2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/lastbld2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/lastbld2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13976" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./lbowling.zip</path>
		<name>League Bowling</name>
		<desc>The lanes are crowded every night with Big Time Pin Slammin' action! You call the shots selecting a right or left handed bowler. Determine ball weight, and develop the skills of the pro's as you skillfully throw a variety of shots that you control. So pop some refreshments and settle into this indoor sport like you've never seen before!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/lbowling.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/lbowling.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/lbowling.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Bowling</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37601" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./legendos.zip</path>
		<name>Legend of Success Joe</name>
		<desc>Joe Yabuki is a little punk wandering the streets. He was spotted by a boxing coach retired from the circuit that sees him as a future champion and decides to manage him. Such is the plot of this boxing game on Neo Geo, adapted from the manga "Ashita no Joe" created by Tetsuya Chiba and Asao Takamori in the 70s.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/legendos.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/legendos.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/legendos.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wave Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Wave Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13957" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./lresort.zip</path>
		<name>Last Resort</name>
		<desc>Last Resort is a 1-2 player horizontal shooter game where you pilot a spacecraft across horizontally scrolling cityscapes and wastelands, while destroying hordes of enemy spacecraft, either metallic or organic, including huge mid- and end-level guardians. Getting power-up pods provide the craft with a movable drone which can be charged up and fired or locked into position and used as an extra gun or 'battering ram'/shield. A clone of R-Type (both one and two), but with much improved graphics and sound</desc>
		<image>./boxart/lresort.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/lresort.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/lresort.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13904" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./magdrop2.zip</path>
		<name>Magical Drop II</name>
		<desc>In Magical Drop II, you control a clown that can grab and throw balloons. You have to match three balloons of the same colour or more vertically to pop them and clear the screen. You can hold multiple balloons of the same colour at once and cause consecutive collisions. There are special balloons that cannot be removed that easily and power-ups that clear entire rows or provide additional help.

Depending of the originating country, there are different game modes:

1. Survival: Play as long as you can - an endless flow of balloons appears at a rapidly increasing speed while you move up levels.

2. Puzzle: You have a limited time to clear a fixed set of balloons before time runs out.

3. VS Mode: Fight the CPU or a fellow player in a direct split-screen duel. Each character has specific item balloons during gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/magdrop2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/magdrop2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/magdrop2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19961124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13883" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./magdrop3.zip</path>
		<name>Magical Drop III</name>
		<desc>This is the third installment in the puzzle frenzy series Magical Drop. In the game you control a clown who throws marbles up on the screen into the cluster of multi-colored marbles, rocks and crystals. The goal is to get three or more of the same color to remove marbles, but you can also grab more than one at the time to create long chain combos and gain better "special" blocks at the top of the screen.

You can play the game in single player modes or versus a friend in versus mode. In versus mode you get to pick your character, much like in a fighting game, each with their own counter attacks and abilities.

For the PSX version, the first Magical Drop was included on a separate disc.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/magdrop3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/magdrop3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/magdrop3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37602" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./maglord.zip</path>
		<name>Magician Lord</name>
		<desc>Magician Lord puts you in charge of Elta, a wizard who has the task of collecting eight books of wisdom from the clutches of Az Atorse, the god of destruction. By collecting the right power-ups along the way, you can transform into different characters, including the Rajin, Samurai, Waterman, Shinobi, Poseidon, and Dragon Warrior. Each character has different abilities. There are eight areas in the game, and each stage ends with you trying to defeat both a guardian and the end-of-area boss (which are basically Atorse's incarnations). One of the first games that demonstrated the graphical abilities of the Neo-Geo.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/maglord.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/maglord.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/maglord.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="78870" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./matrim.zip</path>
		<name>Matrimelee / Shin Gouketsuji Ichizoku Toukon</name>
		<desc>Matrimelee (c) 2002 Playmore.  Revived from the New Power Instinct series, the Goketsuji clan has appeared newly on the MVS Neo-Geo! In addition to the familiar 11 characters, individual fresh 4 join in the heated Head Decision Match. You will be overwhel</desc>
		<image>./boxart/matrim.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/matrim.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/matrim.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory / Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Noise Factory / Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="78920" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./miexchng.zip</path>
		<name>Money Puzzle Exchanger / Money Idol Exchanger</name>
		<desc>Money Puzzle Exchanger (c) 1997 Face.  Handling money has never been so much fun! This incredibly original puzzle game lets you take control of  hilariously designed characters in a cute Japanese superhero theme and boggle your mind with a puzzle system r</desc>
		<image>./boxart/miexchng.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/miexchng.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/miexchng.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FACE</developer>
		<publisher>FACE</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79010" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug - Super Vehicle-001</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug - Super Vehicle-001 (c) 1996 Nazca.  A scrolling 'run-and-gun' platform game for one or two players, Metal Slug is a humorous parody of war and specifically of World War II and the Nazis.  The game features six enemy-packed levels, referred to </desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nazca</developer>
		<publisher>Nazca</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79011" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug2.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 2 - Super Vehicle-001/II</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug 2 - Super Vehicle-001/II (c) 1998 SNK.  The heroes of Metal Slug, Marco and Tarma, are called into action once again to take on the might of General Morden and his armies in this, the first of several sequels to the superb 1996 original. This t</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79012" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug3.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 3</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug 3 (c) 2000 SNK.  The heroes of the first 2 games return once more to do battle with the ever-present General Morden and his vast army. The third game of the series places a greater emphasis on defeating hulking boss characters than the 2 previo</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79013" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug4.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 4</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug 4 (c) 2002 Playmore Corp.  The popular series of side-scrolling action games continues, introducing all-new characters into the plot. The world is now trembling under the fear of cyber terror, as the birth of a deadly new computer virus threate</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug4.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug4.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug4.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mega / Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>Mega / Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79001" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug5.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 5</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug 5 (c) 2003 SNK Playmore.  A research installation developing the next-generation of Metal Slugs is attacked by unknown forces and a disk containing Metal Slug secrets is stolen. Ordered to recover the disk, Marco and Tarma follow in hot pursuit</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug5.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug5.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug5.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79014" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslugx.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug X</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug X - Super Vehicle-001 (c) 1999 SNK.  Originally released to improve upon some of the problems the previous Metal Slug game ("Metal Slug 2 - Super Vehicle-001/II") had, most notably its notorious slowdown, this update also implemented several ch</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslugx.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslugx.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslugx.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79043" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mutnat.zip</path>
		<name>Mutation Nation</name>
		<desc>Mutation Nation (c) 1992 SNK [Shin Nihon Kikaku].  Two lone warriors with an array of special mutant powers attempt to restore order to this futuristic wasteland.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS Hardware Game ID : [Model NGM-014]  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 M</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mutnat.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mutnat.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mutnat.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 2.5D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="60786" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./nam1975.zip</path>
		<name>NAM-1975</name>
		<desc>NAM-1975 (c) 1990 SNK [Shin Nihon Kikaku].  One or two players take control of 2 machine-gun carrying Vietnam vets who must shoot their way through a number of sideways scrolling, Vietnam-themed levels. the players shoot into the screen and aiming is achi</desc>
		<image>./boxart/nam1975.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/nam1975.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/nam1975.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79066" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ncombat.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Combat</name>
		<desc>Ninja Combat (c) 1990 Alpha Denshi.  The ninja castle must be invaded! After you defeat certain boss enemies, they become playable characters as well!  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : [Model NGM-009]  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CP</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ncombat.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ncombat.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ncombat.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi Co.</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Denshi Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79067" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ncommand.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Commando</name>
		<desc>Ninja Commando (c) 1992 Alpha Denshi Co., Ltd.  3 ninjas are sent on a mission to stop a madman named Spider from trying to use a time machine to mess with history. The game is almost like a tongue-in-cheek reworking of "Time Soldiers", which Alpha Denshi</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ncommand.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ncommand.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ncommand.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi Co.</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Denshi Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79075" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./neobombe.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Bomberman</name>
		<desc>Neo Bomber Man (c) 05/1997 Hudson Soft.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0093  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels Scre</desc>
		<image>./boxart/neobombe.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/neobombe.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/neobombe.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="46957" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./neocup98.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Geo Cup '98: The Road To Victory</name>
		<desc>Neo Geo Cup'98 is a football simulation based on the World Cup 1998. This title is a new installment in the series Super Sidekicks and updates all data to focus on the event. In qualification phase or during games knockout, lead one of the 64 available teams to victory.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/neocup98.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/neocup98.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/neocup98.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980528T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79077" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./neodrift.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Drift Out - New Technology</name>
		<desc>Neo Drift Out - New Technology (c) 03/1996 Visco.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0213  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 p</desc>
		<image>./boxart/neodrift.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/neodrift.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/neodrift.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79078" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./neomrdo.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Mr. Do!</name>
		<desc>Neo Mr. Do! (c) 1996 Visco Corp.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0207  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 1 =&gt; [A] Attack enemy  - TRIVIA </desc>
		<image>./boxart/neomrdo.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/neomrdo.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/neomrdo.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79136" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ninjamas.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Master's - haoh-ninpo-cho</name>
		<desc>Ninja Master's Haoh Ninpou-chou (c) 1996 SNK  Criminally overlooked and combo-friendly medieval Japanese fighter with great animation. Ten selectable characters and two end bosses.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 217  Main CPU : 68000 (</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ninjamas.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ninjamas.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ninjamas.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK / SNK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79139" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./nitd.zip</path>
		<name>Nightmare in the Dark</name>
		<desc>Nightmare in the Dark (c) 2000 Eleven / Gavaking.  A peaceful (yet creepy looking!) gravekeeper embarks on a night-shift battle against zombies &amp; other night dwellers in order to put an end to the grave robbing mystery before the local villagers panic! Fe</desc>
		<image>./boxart/nitd.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/nitd.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/nitd.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eleven / Gavaking</developer>
		<publisher>Eleven / Gavaking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79116" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./overtop.zip</path>
		<name>Over Top</name>
		<desc>Over Top (c) 1996 ADK.  You drive different vehicles in this 3D-like 2D game. The backgrounds are quiet nicely done. The task is to finish every race before certain time. There are many hidden shortcuts in this game.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardwa</desc>
		<image>./boxart/overtop.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/overtop.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/overtop.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79180" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./panicbom.zip</path>
		<name>Panic Bomber</name>
		<desc>Panic Bomber - Bomber Man (c) 1995 Eighting.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0073  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels</desc>
		<image>./boxart/panicbom.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/panicbom.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/panicbom.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting / Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Eighting / Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79202" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pbobbl2n.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle Bobble 2 / Bust-A-Move Again</name>
		<desc>Puzzle Bobble 2 (c) 1999 Taito Corp.  MVS re-release. For more information about the game itself, please see the original "Puzzle Bobble 2" (Taito F3 version) entry.  - TECHNICAL -  Game ID : 0248  - TRIVIA -  This game is known in US as "Bust-A-Move Agai</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pbobbl2n.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pbobbl2n.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pbobbl2n.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito (SNK license)</developer>
		<publisher>Taito (SNK license)</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43539" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pbobblen.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle Bobble</name>
		<desc>The first in the hugely successful puzzle series from Taito, Puzzle Bobble is a game for 1 or 2 players in which the aim is to clear each play area of the colored bubbles that litter it. This is achieved by firing bubbl</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pbobblen.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pbobblen.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pbobblen.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Unknown</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79254" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pgoal.zip</path>
		<name>Pleasure Goal / Futsal - 5 on 5 Mini Soccer</name>
		<desc>Pleasure Goal - 5 on 5 Mini Soccer (c) 1996 Saurus.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0219  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pgoal.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pgoal.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pgoal.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42429" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pnyaa.zip</path>
		<name>Pochi and Nyaa</name>
		<desc>Pochi to Nyaa is a cutesy puzzle game where the objective is to match the colored invaders in chains much in the vein of the Sega game "Puyo Puyo Fever". Pochi to Nyaa features three different modes of play: story mode, vs. c</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pnyaa.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pnyaa.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pnyaa.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aiky</developer>
		<publisher>Aiky / Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42464" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./popbounc.zip</path>
		<name>Pop 'n Bounce</name>
		<desc>Pop 'n Bounce (c) 1997 Video System.  A breakout-style game.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0237  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : </desc>
		<image>./boxart/popbounc.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/popbounc.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/popbounc.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Videosystem</developer>
		<publisher>Video System Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42502" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./preisle2.zip</path>
		<name>Prehistoric Isle 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to "Prehistoric Isle in 1930", release more that 10 years after the first one.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/preisle2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/preisle2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/preisle2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Yumekobo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42523" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pspikes2.zip</path>
		<name>Power Spikes II</name>
		<desc>Power Spikes II (c) 1994 Video System.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0068  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 2 =&gt; [A] At service Toss/H</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pspikes2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pspikes2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pspikes2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Video System Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42549" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pulstar.zip</path>
		<name>Pulstar</name>
		<desc>An accomplished and graphically superb sideways scrolling shoot-em-up that borrows many of its visual and gameplay elements from all three games in Irem's legendary "R-Type" series; including the Beam weapon and R-type's infamo</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pulstar.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pulstar.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pulstar.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Aicom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="94165" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./puzzldpr.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle De Pon! R!</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/puzzldpr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/puzzldpr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/puzzldpr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="42564" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./puzzledp.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle De Pon!</name>
		<desc>Drop the target plate before time runs out to clear each stage. To finish the game, clear 39 different stages... </desc>
		<image>./boxart/puzzledp.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/puzzledp.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/puzzledp.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Taito (Visco license)</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79422" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ragnagrd.zip</path>
		<name>Ragnagard / Shin-Oh-Ken</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/ragnagrd.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ragnagrd.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ragnagrd.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="42704" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./rbff1.zip</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury</name>
		<desc>16 characters, some old and some new, breathe new life into the Fatal Fury series.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/rbff1.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/rbff1.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/rbff1.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42705" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./rbff2.zip</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury 2 - The Newcomers</name>
		<desc>23 of the finest South Town fighters in the 7th installment of this SNK game.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/rbff2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/rbff2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/rbff2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42706" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./rbffspec.zip</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury Special</name>
		<desc>'Hey, how's it goin', dude?' More old Fatal favorites return to the bout and bring the total of selectable fighters to 19.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/rbffspec.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/rbffspec.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/rbffspec.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42762" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ridhero.zip</path>
		<name>Riding Hero</name>
		<desc>A Hot Battle Awaits You On The Way To The W.G.P Racing Title! After getting the 'International A License', a young racer battles his way to the Suzuka 8 Hour Race. Featuring 3 ways to play! W.G.P mode, RPG mode or Multi Play mod</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ridhero.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ridhero.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ridhero.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42790" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./roboarmy.zip</path>
		<name>Robo Army</name>
		<desc>Two robotic soldiers attempt to stop the robots and their master from enslaving the human race.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/roboarmy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/roboarmy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/roboarmy.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42819" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./rotd.zip</path>
		<name>Rage of the Dragons</name>
		<desc>Rage of the Dragons is an original fighting game with 14 selectable fighters plus Abubo (sub-boss, hidden character) and Johann (final boss).</desc>
		<image>./boxart/rotd.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/rotd.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/rotd.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Evoga</developer>
		<publisher>Evoga / Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42861" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./s1945p.zip</path>
		<name>Strikers 1945 Plus</name>
		<desc>Strikers 1945 Plus was a remake of Strikers 1945 II for the Neo Geo platform. Plus was the only game in the series with a horizonal monitor configuration.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/s1945p.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/s1945p.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/s1945p.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Psikyo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79411" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsh5sp.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown V Special</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsh5sp.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsh5sp.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsh5sp.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20040000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yuki Enterprise / SNK Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>Yuki Enterprise / SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="79412" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown / Samurai Spirits</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsho.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="79413" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho2.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown II / Shin Samurai Spirits - Haohma</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsho2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="79414" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho3.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown III / Samurai Spirits - Zankurou M</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsho3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="79415" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho4.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown IV - Amakusa's Revenge / Samurai S</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsho4.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho4.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho4.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="42885" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho5.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown V</name>
		<desc>A 5th episode of the Samurai Shodown saga on Neo-Geo with 24 selectable characters plus Poppy (secret character) plus 3 bosses (Sankuro the mid-boss, Yumeji the sub-boss and the general Gaoh as final boss).</desc>
		<image>./boxart/samsho5.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho5.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho5.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yuki Enterprise</developer>
		<publisher>Yuki Enterprise / SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42898" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./savagere.zip</path>
		<name>Savage Reign</name>
		<desc>10 fighters, each brandishing a weapon, fight to have a crack at the Real King Leo. There are 2 planes of action to switch from and in some cases the player can use elements of the background as weapons.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/savagere.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/savagere.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/savagere.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43227" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sdodgeb.zip</path>
		<name>Super Dodge Ball</name>
		<desc>The object is to hit your opponent's player with the ball while avoiding being hit. Once a player has been hit three times, that player is out of the game. The game is won by knocking all the opposing players out of the game.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sdodgeb.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sdodgeb.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sdodgeb.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Leland Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42966" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sengoku.zip</path>
		<name>Sengoku</name>
		<desc>Two warriors, endowed with spiritual gifts, fight to stop the resurrection of the Mad Shogun. Lots of very interesting enemies and beautiful scenery. The player also has the ability to morph into different fighte</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sengoku.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sengoku.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sengoku.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42967" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sengoku2.zip</path>
		<name>Sengoku 2</name>
		<desc>The Mad Shogun rises again, this time taking over various periods in the time stream. Now you're permanently armed with a sword and must save different eras from the wrath of the Mad Shogun!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sengoku2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sengoku2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sengoku2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42968" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sengoku3.zip</path>
		<name>Sengoku 3</name>
		<desc>Taking quite a different approach than the previous 2 Sengoku games, the 3rd in the series introduces 4 characters and a new chain combo system. 2 bosses, when defeated, can also be selected for battle for the final 2 stages.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sengoku3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sengoku3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sengoku3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Noise Factory / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43049" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./shocktr2.zip</path>
		<name>Shock Troopers - 2nd Squad</name>
		<desc>More of an update than a full-blown sequel, Shock Troopers - 2nd Squad picks up where the first game - released a year earlier - left off. Once again, one or two players face the might of a terrorist army who are </desc>
		<image>./boxart/shocktr2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/shocktr2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/shocktr2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43050" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./shocktro.zip</path>
		<name>Shock Troopers</name>
		<desc>TheBigL1 rates this game: 5/5This overhead run n' gun shooter has eight different characters you can play as, who all have different weapons and movement speed.
Tapping the A button lets you sweep your shots with your guns, and you can hold the button to strafe. If you press B you'll do a rolling dodge, which you can use to evade enemy bullets. You press C to use your secondary weapon, which is very strong but has limited ammo. Each character has a different default gun and secondary weapon.
Enemy attacks will deplete your health gauge, and if it drops to zero then you'll need to put in another credit to keep going. You can find food and first-aid kits to heal yourself, and before starting each level you get some health back.
Special guns are found throughout the levels, and can be used until they run out of ammo or you get another gun. There are also pickups to replenish your secondary weapon, and attacking enemies in close-range will make them drop point bonuses.
When starting the game you can use one character or a team of three. If you choose a team of three, you can press D during play to switch between them.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/shocktro.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/shocktro.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/shocktro.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43163" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./socbrawl.zip</path>
		<name>Soccer Brawl</name>
		<desc>Soccer Brawl (c) 1992 SNK.  A futuristic soccer game.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID: [Model NGM-031]  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  [SNK MVS Neo-Geo Controls] 2 players - 4 buttons</desc>
		<image>./boxart/socbrawl.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/socbrawl.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/socbrawl.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37641" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sonicwi2.zip</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters 2</name>
		<desc>Aero Fighters 2 is a vertically-scrolling shooter in the same vein as 1942 and similar games. It supports up to two players and  has 8 different aircraft to choose from, each equipped with unique primary and secondary weapons. Power-ups upgrade the look, power, size and shape of the shots. Bombs activate a special power that usually wipes off the enemies on the screen. The game has a total of 10 stages (Japan, Brazil, Atlantic, U.S.A., France, Australia, Himalayas, Mexico, Hawaii and Space), all of them with a boss battle.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sonicwi2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sonicwi2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sonicwi2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37642" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sonicwi3.zip</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters 3</name>
		<desc>Aero Fighters 3 is a vertically-scrolling shooter in the same vein as 1942 and similar games. It supports up to two players and  has 10 different aircraft to choose from, each equipped with unique primary and secondary weapons. Power-ups upgrade the look, power, size and shape of the shots. Bombs activate a special power that usually wipes off the enemies on the screen. The game has a total of 8 stages placed on several countries (Japan, Germany, Libya, Egypt, Pacific, U.S.A., England, France, Panama, Thailand, Ukraine, Atlantic and Space), all of them with a boss battle.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sonicwi3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sonicwi3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sonicwi3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19951117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43251" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./spinmast.zip</path>
		<name>Spin Master</name>
		<desc>Johnny &amp; Tom, two treasure seekers must save their friend Mary from the evil Mad Doctor and his army of goofy-dressed henchmen, as well as gather the map pieces in order to find the biggest treasure in the world at the</desc>
		<image>./boxart/spinmast.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/spinmast.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/spinmast.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43312" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ssideki.zip</path>
		<name>Super Sidekicks</name>
		<desc>Super Sidekicks (c) 1992 SNK.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 052  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 2 =&gt; Offense &gt; [A] Long kick/Shoot, </desc>
		<image>./boxart/ssideki.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ssideki.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ssideki.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43313" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ssideki2.zip</path>
		<name>Super Sidekicks 2 - The World Championship</name>
		<desc>Super Sidekicks 2 - The World Championship (c) 1994 SNK.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 061  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 3 =&gt; Atta</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ssideki2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ssideki2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ssideki2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43314" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ssideki3.zip</path>
		<name>Super Sidekicks 3 - The Next Glory</name>
		<desc>Super Sidekicks is the 3rd game in the famous Super Sidekicks series of soccer games. Featuring 6 competition modes for 64 world wide teams. Utilizes Digitized Trace Animation and 3-D camera angled shots f</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ssideki3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ssideki3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ssideki3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43315" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ssideki4.zip</path>
		<name>The Ultimate 11 - The SNK Football Championship</name>
		<desc>The Ultimate 11 - SNK Football Championship (c) 1996 SNK.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 215  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz)a Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 3 =&gt; At</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ssideki4.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ssideki4.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ssideki4.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43342" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./stakwin.zip</path>
		<name>Stakes Winner</name>
		<desc>Stakes Winner (c) 1995 Saurus.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0088  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels Screen refres</desc>
		<image>./boxart/stakwin.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/stakwin.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/stakwin.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43343" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./stakwin2.zip</path>
		<name>Stakes Winner 2</name>
		<desc>Stakes Winner 2 (c) 1996 Saurus.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0227  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels Screen refr</desc>
		<image>./boxart/stakwin2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/stakwin2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/stakwin2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43394" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./strhoop.zip</path>
		<name>Street Hoop</name>
		<desc>A basketball game from the streets. Choose from one of ten countries and compete in three-on-three slamdunkin' action.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/strhoop.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/strhoop.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/strhoop.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43433" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./superspy.zip</path>
		<name>The Super Spy</name>
		<desc>Infiltrate terrorist hideouts and beat up the bad guys in this gender-bending (but still good) first-person beat-em-up with RPG elements.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/superspy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/superspy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/superspy.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43466" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./svc.zip</path>
		<name>SVC Chaos : SNK vs. Capcom</name>
		<desc>A one-on-one fighting game - the collaboration between Capcom and SNK - pits seventeen well-known SNK combatants against seventeen of Capcom's most famous game characters.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/svc.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/svc.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/svc.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43674" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./tophuntr.zip</path>
		<name>Top Hunter - Roddy &amp; Cathy</name>
		<desc>An unique action platform game that feature Roddy &amp; Cathy, 2 powerful bounty hunters that are determined to wipe out the space pirate army! Features excellent 2-D graphics &amp; plenty of secrets to find!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/tophuntr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/tophuntr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/tophuntr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43707" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./tpgolf.zip</path>
		<name>Top Player's Golf</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/tpgolf.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/tpgolf.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/tpgolf.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43713" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./trally.zip</path>
		<name>Thrash Rally</name>
		<desc>Thrash Rally is a top-down perspective rally racing game for one or two players. Each race begins with players asked to choose a vehicle in which to race, with each offering a different balance between handling, accele</desc>
		<image>./boxart/trally.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/trally.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/trally.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Denshi Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43780" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./turfmast.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Turf Masters</name>
		<desc>An absolutely superb arcade golf game in which one or two players choose from a selection of six different golfers, each possessing different strengths and weaknesses. Four eighteen-hole golf courses are available: German</desc>
		<image>./boxart/turfmast.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/turfmast.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/turfmast.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nazca</developer>
		<publisher>Nazca</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43808" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./twinspri.zip</path>
		<name>Twinkle Star Sprites</name>
		<desc>Competitive shooter with flavors of Galaga, Fighting Games, and Sailor Moon.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/twinspri.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/twinspri.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/twinspri.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ADK / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43813" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./tws96.zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo World Soccer '96</name>
		<desc>An excellent soccer game featuring great graphics, tons of voiceovers and some of the world's best football nations.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/tws96.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/tws96.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/tws96.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43958" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./viewpoin.zip</path>
		<name>Viewpoint</name>
		<desc>Viewpoint is an isometric shooter developed by Sammy and published by SNK for release on various platforms.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/viewpoin.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/viewpoin.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/viewpoin.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sammy Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy / Aicom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Diagonal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44022" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wakuwak7.zip</path>
		<name>Waku Waku 7</name>
		<desc>Sunsoft's second 2D fighter for the NeoGeo system.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wakuwak7.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wakuwak7.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wakuwak7.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44061" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wh1.zip</path>
		<name>World Heroes</name>
		<desc>8 heroes from different time periods compete to thwart Geegus, the evil alien end boss! Includes an extremely fun and unique death match mode!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wh1.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wh1.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wh1.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Denshi Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44062" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wh2.zip</path>
		<name>World Heroes 2</name>
		<desc>14 characters and 2 end bosses do battle in normal or death match modes.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wh2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wh2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wh2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44063" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wh2j.zip</path>
		<name>World Heroes 2 Jet</name>
		<desc>This update of World Heroes 2 introduces two new characters, Ryofu and Jack and 2 new modes of play - the Tournament and the Forging of Warriors.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wh2j.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wh2j.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wh2j.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ADK / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44069" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./whp.zip</path>
		<name>World Heroes Perfect</name>
		<desc>A new button layout for the final game in the series greets the 16 fighters, 1 hidden fighter and 2 end bosses.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/whp.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/whp.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/whp.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ADK / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44100" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wjammers.zip</path>
		<name>Windjammers</name>
		<desc>Windjammers (also known as Flying Power Disc in Japan) is a fast pace, sport arcade game released by Data East on the Neo Geo arcade system in 1994 and later on the Wii Virtual Console in Japan on June 22, 2010. Following the bankruptcy of Data East, the intellectual rights for this game were acquired by Paon</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wjammers.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wjammers.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wjammers.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44196" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./zedblade.zip</path>
		<name>Zed Blade</name>
		<desc>Zed Blade is a sideways scrolling shoot-em-up for one or two players. Players can chose from three different ships, each with varying speeds.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/zedblade.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/zedblade.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/zedblade.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NMK</developer>
		<publisher>NMK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44223" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./zupapa.zip</path>
		<name>Zupapa!</name>
		<desc>Is a 2001 release of SNK for MVS. It's pretty much a puzzler / screen-cleaning game with bright and colourful optics and simple gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/zupapa.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/zupapa.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/zupapa.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37561" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./2020bb.fba</path>
		<name>2020 Super Baseball</name>
		<desc>In the year 2020, baseball finally evolved. There is no longer conventional professional baseball in 2020. Baseball designed by the Super Baseball Association has been very popular and is the best sport.

However, the truth is that the association has used a colossal sum of money to promote Super Baseball as show business. They have manipulated each player's ability using the control computer to secretly decide victory or defeat in every game. The players who knew this removed the connecting parts of the computer to play their own game of baseball. Finally, a fair game is going to be played at Cyber Egg Stadium.

In 2020 Super Baseball is a fast-paced game with new rules, where you can select 1 of 12 individual men, women, or robot players. During play, you can make your team stronger with prizes earned from amazing catches.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/2020bb.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/2020bb.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/2020bb.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pallas</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13937" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./3countb.fba</path>
		<name>3 Count Bout</name>
		<desc>3 Count Bout is a one-on-one fighting game. Choose from ten wrestlers who have their own power attacks. There are ten rounds in the game, and each one of them has you fighting other wrestlers that are much tougher than the previous ones. You defeat each one by biting, kicking, and performing other moves to the point where their damage meter is empty. But just because it is empty doesn't mean that you win. You have to pin him for the infamous-three count. Also features competitive play and tag match battles.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/3countb.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/3countb.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/3countb.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>UPL</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37563" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./alpham2.fba</path>
		<name>Alpha Mission II</name>
		<desc>The lunar nightmare of a bloody 200-year space war was thought to be over in the "original" ALPHA MISSION. But now with the advent of more technically sophisticated weapons, the evil "Fulvar" and his "Seven Star Alliance" have returned to destroy all planets that stand in their way of the ultimate target... Earth! Now in the year of 2525! Your mission as pilot of the new SYD-FX fighter is to use every weapon at your disposal to rid the galaxy once and for all of the evil that now dominates and threatens Earth. So suit up, hold your breath, and stand ready for unbelievable graphics and stereo sound that'll suck you into the far reaches of deep, dark inner space. Be prepared... you may never come back!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/alpham2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/alpham2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/alpham2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13927" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./androdun.fba</path>
		<name>Andro Dunos</name>
		<desc>The invasion of an unknown life source is getting worse. Nobody knows if the defensive line or the heart of the enemy base is ruined first. With the people's hope, the most advanced fighter will be dispatched into multi-scrolling space.

Fight your way through seven stages in this horizontal-scrolling game, and defeat a boss at the end of each one. You start the game with four main weapons, which you can switch from with the click of a button. Some of these weapons are more powerful than others. You can also fire off a charged shot if your main weapon level is two or greater, simply by holding down the fire button for about two seconds. Using charged shots can do more damage to an enemy ship. If you happen to die, you will lose one power level from all four weapons. If all your lives are lost and are forced to continue, you will start again with your main weapon on the second power level and all three sub-weapons on the first power level.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/androdun.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/androdun.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/androdun.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920717T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37564" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./aodk.fba</path>
		<name>Aggressors of Dark Kombat</name>
		<desc>Aggressors of Dark Kombat is another one-on-one street fighting beat 'em up from the Neo-Geo's seemingly endless library of fighters.

It pits 8 fighters of different styles and strengths against each other in a tournament to see who's the toughest mofo on the streets of Tokyo. Your objective as usual is to deplete your opponent's health bar within the time limit by using your basic attacks and special moves (triggered by specific controller motions) while avoiding his moves and attacks.

Unique to Aggressors of Dark Kombat is the combination of traditional side-scrolling beat 'em up elements, meaning characters can freely move in an isometric space instead of being restricted to a single plane of movement. Weapons and throw-able items are usually thrown into the arena by the crowds and you can pick them up and wield them for added damage. Additionally, matches are 1-round only affairs, with an extended multi-layered health bar that allows for longer rounds than usual.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/aodk.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/aodk.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/aodk.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19940826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37565" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./aof.fba</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting</name>
		<desc>The storyline of Art of Fighting takes place in 1978. Ryo Sakazaki and Robert Garcia set out to find Ryo's sister, Yuri, who was kidnapped by Mr. Big. Mr. Big took Yuri to entice Takuma Sakazaki, Ryo's father and originator of Kyokugen Karate, and also because Ryo refused to work for Big. After Ryo &amp; Robert defeat Mr. Big, they face the enigmatic Mr. Karate. Art of Fighting's story ends with a cliff-hanger; Yuri is about to disclose the true identity of Mr. Karate as their father Takuma.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/aof.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/aof.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/aof.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19921211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37566" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./aof2.fba</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting 2</name>
		<desc>In this sequel to the original Art of Fighting, and prequel to the original Fatal Fury, we learn that Mr. Karate, the final boss of the original game, behind the mask, is really Takuma Sakazaki, Ryo and Yuri's father, that Takuma was being used by Geese Howard for his own evil intentions, and that Mr. Big was the one who had originally kidnapped Yuri.

Many of the problems that existed in the first game have been fixed in this installment (it is easier to execute special moves, you no longer have only Ryo or Robert to choose from in 1 player mode, etc.).

The entire cast from the first Art of Fighting is here (with the exceptions of Todo and Mr. Karate), along with a few new characters: Takuma Sakazaki, Ryo and Yuri's father; Yuri Sakazaki, Takuma's daughter and Ryo's sister; Eiji Kisaragi, a sworn enemy of the Sakazakis; Temjin, a Mongolian trucker; and a younger version of Geese Howard, whom you face as the last boss if you beat the game without losing a round.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/aof2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/aof2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/aof2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="40019" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./aof3.fba</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting 3 - The Path of the Warrior</name>
		<desc>Art of Fighting 3 featured a new cast of characters with the exception of Ryo and Robert. Yuri Sakazaki is seen in the game, but only as a side character in Ryo and Robert's story mode.
The story switched focus from the Sakazakis to Robert Garcia. Garcia disappears to search for an old childhood friend, Freia Lawrence, and he tracks her to GlassHill, Mexico. Freia is wanted by the game's main antagonist, Wyler, to complete a powerful elixir that was created by his and Freia's fathers. The drug affects users in a similar manner as the potion in The Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde.
One of the game's characters, Kasumi Todoh, became a part of The King of Fighters cast. This game is the only one in the series to have a CD Drama Arranged Soundtrack.[2]
It was re-released for the Wii's Virtual Console in North America on 21 March 2013 at a cost of 900 Wii Points.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/aof3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/aof3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/aof3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37568" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./bangbead.fba</path>
		<name>Bang Bead</name>
		<desc>Bang Bead, known in Japan as Bang Beads, is a 2001 ball-and-paddle game developed and published by Visco exclusively for the arcade cabinet known as the SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware. It combines the genres of the Magnavox Odyssey Tennis game, Atari's Pong and Breakout arcades, and Nintendo's Spitball Sparky of the Game &amp; Watch series. You can select from 9 characters and play against another player or the computer. Knock out the stars behind the other player then get the bouncing ball through to win the round.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/bangbead.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/bangbead.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/bangbead.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37569" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./bjourney.fba</path>
		<name>Blue's Journey</name>
		<desc>The planet of Raguy was once beautiful and peaceful, but all hell broke loose when it was invaded by the Daruma tribe. The pollution started to spread through the city. Blue was summoned to get rid of the Daruma tribe, and save Raguy from the Daruma Empire that has turned the inhabitants into slaves.

You control Blue, who only has one weapon to deal with the Darumas. You can use his leaf to whip enemies upside-down, and hurl these enemies at others. Along the way, you can get flowers for use at the shop to buy items that will help you along the way. These items include flower honey (increases stamina), swim fins (easier swimming), light safe (protects all your items), spikes, and ocarinas. Later in the game, you can also get the shopkeeper to sing you a song. This helps you break curses that are placed on you by a witch.You will also interact with other characters along the way that can also help you if you tell the truth.

You exit each stage by jumping on a huge plant. The higher up you are on this plant, the more points you are awarded. Every two or so stages, you have to defeat a boss before a guy in a devil suit offers you something. You can refuse or accept the other. If you accept the offer, you will have to pull one of four strings that will give you a life ball, more stamina, 30 flowers, cocoons, or five flowers.

You are on a time limit. If you run out of time, a black creature appears out of nowhere, and starts firing "bird" missiles at you.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/bjourney.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/bjourney.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/bjourney.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13893" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./blazstar.fba</path>
		<name>Blazing Star</name>
		<desc>The unofficial sequel to Pulstar, Blazing Star is again a horizontal-scrolling shoot-'em-up. One or two players proceed along levels, each with a boss enemy at the end, trying to redeem the humankind. There are six ships to choose from, each with its own pilot (four of them females), weapons and characteristics of movement. Each ship has its own types of shots, but also a standard shot, charged shot (more powerful) and split shot (a charged shot can be parted into more bullets, lowering the power of each bullet while widening the fire range).</desc>
		<image>./boxart/blazstar.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/blazstar.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/blazstar.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13877" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./breakers.fba</path>
		<name>Breakers</name>
		<desc>In Breakers, choose one of eight fighters who have their own moves and special attacks. There are eight stages in the game, and each stage has two battles. The object of each battle is to drain your opponent's energy in order to win the battle. If there is a draw, a third battle takes place. If the time limit expires, the player with the less energy loses the battle. Once you have completed all eight stages, you will face a opponent that is much tougher than previous ones. Different endings and in-game dialog are viewed depending on the character that you select.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/breakers.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/breakers.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/breakers.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19961217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37570" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./breakrev.fba</path>
		<name>Breakers Revenge</name>
		<desc>8 initially selectable characters face off to become the Tae Kwon Do master! After defeating the absolutely WACKY Master Taekuk, he becomes selectable as well to face off against end boss Karate Kenji.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/breakrev.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/breakrev.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/breakrev.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37571" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./bstars.fba</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars Professional</name>
		<desc>Baseball Stars Professional is the follow-up to Baseball Stars for the Nintendo Entertainment System, and features comic-style graphics. Choose from a variety of teams that include Celestial Planets, Heavenly Bodies, Shadow Demons, Battle Knights, Fabulous Superstars, and many others. Then select the field where the game is to be held: The SNK stadium or the SNK dome. Each field has the same dimensions, but their capacity varies. The game is played the same way as normal baseball. Features a VS. mode in which two players can play against each other.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/bstars.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/bstars.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/bstars.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13951" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./bstars2.fba</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars 2</name>
		<desc>This follow up to Baseball Stars Professional features a fast-paced arcade style baseball with six fictitious teams, each with their own strengths and weaknesses.  There are two difficulties of play: Beginner, which automatically fields the ball for the player while Exciting has the player do the field manually.  Additionally, there are two main modes of play where in the single player mode the player will compete in a fifteen-team tournament or go head-to-head against a friend in a multiplayer mode.

The standard rules of baseball still apply, but it adds power-ups that the player can pick up and use during the game, such as the ability for their pitcher to throw faster or their batter to hit better. They can also substitute a player during the game, but are limited to three substitutions per game. The game is shown through 2D graphics with comic-style cutscenes to illustrate the action, such as dramatic catches and home runs that will pop-up during the game.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/bstars2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/bstars2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/bstars2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37572" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./burningf.fba</path>
		<name>Burning Fight</name>
		<desc>The Castella family from the Metro City started ruining the peaceful city of Osaka with the violent Japanese group, "Heiwa-gumi". To stop the fight, Metro police detectives dispatched two dangerous characters, Duke and Billy, to Japan. With the support of the famous Japanese detective Ryu, they decided to rush into the enemy's fortress. Ruthless violence in the neon lights of Osaka. Will there be an end to this war?

Burning Fight is a side-scrolling street-fighting game similar to Final Fight. As Duke, Billy, or Ryu, you must fight your way through the various locations in Osaka. At the start of the game, you can only use your fists to deal with gangs, but by by breaking things like phone booths and street signs along the way, you can get new weapons and more health. At the end of each location, you will have to defeat a boss in order to continue the mission.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/burningf.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/burningf.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/burningf.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13924" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./crsword.fba</path>
		<name>Crossed Swords</name>
		<desc>As a knight, you must travel the countryside fighting monsters and bandits using your sword and shield. When you enter combat the view changes to a pseudo 1st-person perspective where the body of your knight is outlined so that you can see the creatures that you are fighting. When enemies have been defeated, they drop money and power-ups. There are seven chapters in the game, and each chapter (except one) starts with you entering a merchant's shop and buying weapons using the money that you have collected so far. There are also alternate paths which take you to different parts of the game. At the start of the game, you may choose a chapter (from one to three only) you want to start at.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/crsword.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/crsword.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/crsword.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13938" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ctomaday.fba</path>
		<name>Captain Tomaday</name>
		<desc>A comical vertically scrolling shoot'em up starring a mutated tomato who punches the enemy and can transform to other weird characters.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ctomaday.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ctomaday.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ctomaday.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13931" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./cyberlip.fba</path>
		<name>Cyber-Lip</name>
		<desc>Cyber-Lip is a 1-2 player side-scrolling game where you must fight your way through several areas, and defeat a boss at the end of each one. Along the way, you can pick up a variety of weapons along the way, and use them against the invaders. By destroying certain enemies, you receive a "core bot", which is a ring that surrounds you, and when this touches the invaders, they are destroyed. Time is against you. When it expires, you lose a life.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/cyberlip.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/cyberlip.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/cyberlip.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37573" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./doubledr.fba</path>
		<name>Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>Released around the same time as the film of the same name and loosely based on its story, this installment in the Double Dragon series also moves away from the traditional roam-the-streets-fighting to a pure one-on-one fighter. There are ten characters to choose from, including Billy and Jimmy and the game has colorful interactive backgrounds, screen zooming, over-the-top special moves and with the inclusion of double jumps, combos, charges for the losing player and counter hits, there is plenty of room for advanced fighting strategies.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/doubledr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/doubledr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/doubledr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="41092" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./eightman.fba</path>
		<name>Eight Man</name>
		<desc>Eightman (c) 1991 SNK [Shin Nihon Kikaku].  A side-scrolling beat'em up / platform game.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS Hardware Game ID : [Model NGM-025]  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  [SNK MVS Neo</desc>
		<image>./boxart/eightman.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/eightman.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/eightman.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK / Pallas</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37575" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fatfursp.fba</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury Special</name>
		<desc>Fatal Fury Special is an improved version of SNK's 2D one-on-one fighter Fatal Fury 2. It's a conversion of the 1993 arcade game of the same name. The objective is still to win the tournament by defeating all other fighters including end boss Wolfgang Krauser. Fatal Fury Special features a fairly large selection of fighters. A new Count Down mode (defeat as many opponents as possible in 3 minutes).Extra color schemes for every character.New &amp; improved background graphics.Dolby Surround Sound support.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fatfursp.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fatfursp.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fatfursp.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37576" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fatfury1.fba</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury - King of Fighters</name>
		<desc>Southtown City plays host to the King of Fighters Tournament. Andy &amp; Terry Bogard take part in the tournament cause winning the tournament is the only way they can defeat Geese Howard. Geese Howard controls Southtown City and killed their father several years ago. Also taking part is Joe Higashi, a Japanese kickboxer. Select either Joe, Andy or Terry, visit several locations in Southtown City and win that tournament!

Fatal Fury is a 2D fighter and is the first game in a series of one-on-one fighting games by SNK. It's a conversion of the original Fatal Fury arcade game. This first game does not yet feature the series' trademark pseudo 3D mode (which allows you to move between the foreground &amp; background while fighting). Includes a two-player vs. mode.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fatfury1.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fatfury1.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fatfury1.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37577" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fatfury2.fba</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury 2</name>
		<desc>Again, the Lone Wolves return!

Geese Howard may have been defeated, but that doesn't mean all is peaceful. A new opponent, Wolfgang Krauser, has come forth to begin a new Fatal Fury tournament. The Lone Wolves return, with new faces amongst them. Only one can be declared the winner though.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fatfury2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fatfury2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fatfury2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37578" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fatfury3.fba</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury 3 - Road to the Final Victory</name>
		<desc>An adaptation of the Neo-Geo fighting game.  2-D scrolling one-on-one fighter with pseudo-3D aspects (that allows for players to "escape" holds, throws, and other attacks.)  Part of the incestuously-popular SNK fighting game pantheon...
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fatfury3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fatfury3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fatfury3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13966" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fbfrenzy.fba</path>
		<name>Football Frenzy</name>
		<desc>You'll never play another football game again, after you play Football Frenzy! Football Frenzy, with on-going play-by-play announcing, is hard-hitting action at its best! You will hear, in full stereo, every bone-crushing tackle and helmet-to-helmet, metal-on-metal hit. The piercing grunts and groans of players sacrificing their bodies for the team puts you right on the field with them! The camera zooms give you the most dazzling close-ups ever seen. So, bring your pads and helmet! Tournament mode, cinematic displays and over 10 teams to choose from make this football package complete. Play against the computer or a friend in this 46-MEG bone-jarring gridiron great... Football Frenzy!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fbfrenzy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fbfrenzy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fbfrenzy.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37579" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./fightfev.fba</path>
		<name>Fight Fever</name>
		<desc>There are 8 characters to select from and two boss characters (the first boss character is only playable in two player mode). The object of the game is to win two matches out of three. Each character has a set of moves in addition to two basic punches and kicks. Each character also has a super move called a "Danger Move", which are similar to the Desperation Moves from Fatal Fury 2. Players also have the ability to taunt others, but unlike games such as Art of Fighting, this has no effect and would actually leave the player open to attacks.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/fightfev.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/fightfev.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/fightfev.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Viccom</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13917" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./flipshot.fba</path>
		<name>Battle Flip Shot</name>
		<desc>Battle Flip Shot is an arcade game that mixes elements of Pong with Japanese character design.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/flipshot.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/flipshot.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/flipshot.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37580" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./galaxyfg.fba</path>
		<name>Galaxy Fight</name>
		<desc>People have prayed to the gods, but the devil descends from the sky. Your mission is to defeat Felden Kryse, ruler of the underworld. The fantastic challenge ferociously unfolds on eight different planets. Screen image changes on-the-fly to zoom in and out based on how the battle unfolds. Use Dash to your utmost advantage, and speed through the field of infinity.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/galaxyfg.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/galaxyfg.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/galaxyfg.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13945" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ganryu.fba</path>
		<name>Ganryu</name>
		<desc>One month has passed since Musashi defeated his sworn enemy, Kojiro. Musashi was on the way to Kyoto, where his beloved Otsu was waiting for him. Around this time, many abductions had occurred by a mysterious group of ninjas, and Otsu was one of the missing. What is the true purpose of these ninjas? The time to fight has come again for Musashi!!

You must guide Musashi or his sister, Suzame, around several locations defeating a horde of ninjas with only a sword. Weapon power-ups and life bonuses can be collected along the way. You can jump high and use your grappling hook to attach to and climb some ceilings, as well as attaching yourself to faraway objects. At the end of each location, you must defeat a guardian in order to continue the game. Cut-scenes are viewed between locations.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ganryu.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ganryu.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ganryu.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37581" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./garou.fba</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury: Mark of the Wolves</name>
		<desc>It's been several years since Geese Howard was defeated in a battle with Terry Bogard, a young man looking to avenge his father. Rather than looking to be saved from death after falling off his office balcony, Geese instead decided to die, and left behind his young son, Rock. Terry took Rock in and became like a big brother to him, raising the boy throughout his life.

Now Rock is a teenager, and Terry is a man in his 30s, and both are about to come together in a new clash...new faces and old come together for the greatest battle yet!
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/garou.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/garou.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/garou.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20000225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37582" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ghostlop.fba</path>
		<name>Ghostlop</name>
		<desc>Ghost Lop is an excellent Ghostbusters themed puzzle game by Data East from 1996. It combines the fast action of an Arkanoid style game, with the quick thinking of a Bust-A-Move type game. The game was re-considered for release in 2001, but SNK's untimely demise later that same year may have ended that possibility. Data East was best known for its' Chain Reaction / Magical Drop series of puzzle games, and even later included the Ghostlop characters in one of the later releases for modern home game systems.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ghostlop.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ghostlop.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ghostlop.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13906" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./goalx3.fba</path>
		<name>Goal! Goal! Goal!</name>
		<desc>A soccer game with all the right ingredients, skill, flair, passion, and of course, GOALS! With 28 national teams to choose from, compete in a tournament to become the best soccer nation in the world. Get past the opening group stage and go on to a round-robin elimination stage where failure is not an option. To help you on your way, hold down the shoot button until the power bar fills up and you can do a POWERFUL SUPER SHOT!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/goalx3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/goalx3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/goalx3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="41498" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./gowcaizr.fba</path>
		<name>Voltage Fighter - Gowcaizer</name>
		<desc>An anime style fighting game that takes place in the Year 2010 in Tron City. In this city, there is a school for special students called the Belnar Institute. Isato Kaiza, the hero of the story, is a student at</desc>
		<image>./boxart/gowcaizr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/gowcaizr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/gowcaizr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Technos Japan</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37584" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./gpilots.fba</path>
		<name>Ghost Pilots</name>
		<desc>Ghost Pilots is an overhead military plane shooter, in which you must shoot down fighter jets by either using bullets or bombs. Once you have killed enough fighter jets, you will have to defeat a boss fighter jet in order to continue. After some stages, you must select a route to continue your journey on. Power-ups can be collected that will increase your firepower, and stars can be obtained for extra points.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/gpilots.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/gpilots.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/gpilots.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shoot'em Up</developer>
		<publisher>Shoot'em Up</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37585" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./gururin.fba</path>
		<name>Gururin</name>
		<desc>Your goal is to make three people of the same color line up and disappear--but to do that, you won't flip the people around as they fall but rather rotate the entire pit once they've landed. Like clothes in a dryer, you've got to flip the whole playfield around and try to match up the midgets as they slide down to the bottom of the screen, reorganizing themselves as they go.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/gururin.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/gururin.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/gururin.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FACE</developer>
		<publisher>FACE</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="87607" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ironclad.fba</path>
		<name>Choutetsu Brikin'ger - Iron clad</name>
		<desc>Ironclad is a side scrolling shooter developed by Saurus in 1996. Ironclad was first shown in its native MVS cartridge format at the March 1996 ACME show in Orlando, Florida. I saw and played the game at the show. We always knew therefore that at the very least, one proto was available on the MVS format. Although the game saw release on the NEOGEO CD system, it was never officially released in either the MVS or HOME cartridge formats. Ironclad was the most sought after of all the CD-protos because of its appeal to shoot 'em up fans. This was most likely why it had coincidentally caused the largest number of false claims; more then any other proto cartridge! 13 years later, in November of 2009, SNK finally released the native ROM data for the game and as a result we finally got the game and can now enjoy it forever!</desc>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="41839" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./irrmaze.fba</path>
		<name>The Irritating Maze</name>
		<desc>The Irritating Maze (c) 1997 SNK.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0236  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels Screen ref</desc>
		<image>./boxart/irrmaze.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/irrmaze.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/irrmaze.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK / Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="41913" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./joyjoy.fba</path>
		<name>Puzzled</name>
		<desc>Two cute little kids need you to help rescue their villages. Their way is blocked by rows of blocks. Destroy the rows of blocks and help them reach the head God so their villages can be saved.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/joyjoy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/joyjoy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/joyjoy.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Fall</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37589" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kabukikl.fba</path>
		<name>Far East of Eden - Kabuki Klash</name>
		<desc>"Kabuki Klash" is a 2D fighting game that features characters from the famous Japanese role-playing series  Tengai Makyou, also known as Far East of Eden. The heroes of the three first Tengai Makyou games must participate in a tournament and find out who is the most skillful fighter in the magical land of Jipang (which is very similar to the medieval Japan). The characters include well-known Far East of Eden heroes such as Ziria, Manjimaru, Kabuki, Orochimaru, and others - a total of eight playable characters. During the fights, you can either punch, kick, or use special attacks, that require a precise usage of buttons and also deplete your magic gauge. There are random items (such as healing potions) thrown on the battle field while you are fighting, which you can pick up.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kabukikl.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kabukikl.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kabukikl.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19951123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37590" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./karnovr.fba</path>
		<name>Karnov's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Karnov's Revenge is a 2-D Street Fighter II clone from Data East. Choose one of 13 fighters from around the world to play as, each with their unique moves and special attacks. As usual, there are two rounds in each stage, and the object of each round is to drain your opponent's energy in order to win the battle. If there is a tie after two rounds, a third round is played. There is a time limit, and if this expires, the player with the less energy loses.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/karnovr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/karnovr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/karnovr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK of America</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13920" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kizuna.fba</path>
		<name>Kizuna Encounter Super Tag Battle</name>
		<desc>Fight Alone!
Competition or Team Battles. The Tage Battle of a Lifetime Begins!
Or Fight with a Friend!

Why Do You Fight?! For money? For glory? For...?!
The Fate of 10 of the World's Mightiest Warriors Rests on the Grand Ambitions of King Lion!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kizuna.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kizuna.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kizuna.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19961108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42023" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof2000.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2000</name>
		<desc>34 characters, plus the popular striker system, await to be selected to team up and defeat the mighty Zero and his incredible bladed coat!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof2000.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof2000.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof2000.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42024" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof2001.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2001</name>
		<desc>With the largest KOF lineup totaling at 40 characters, newcomers Eolith do a great job at delivering high quality fighting action along with one of the most difficult pairs of bosses in fighting game history!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof2001.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof2001.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof2001.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eolith Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Eolith / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42025" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof2002.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2002</name>
		<desc>Revived 3 on 3 battles and new MAX Activation System enable you to get more and more exciting showdowns.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof2002.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof2002.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof2002.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eolith Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Eolith / Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="41975" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof2003.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2003</name>
		<desc>The King of Fighters 2003 turned out to be the last game in the series released on the Neo-Geo console. Ports with 3D backgrounds were made for other systems. Tag-team gameplay was added and the game introduced lot of new characters.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof2003.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof2003.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof2003.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42027" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof94.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '94</name>
		<desc>24 selectable characters in fixed teams of three clash to defeat Rugal Bernstein.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof94.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof94.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof94.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42028" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof95.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '95</name>
		<desc>8 teams comprised of 3 characters each square off again to take out Rugal Bernstein.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof95.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof95.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof95.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42029" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof96.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '96</name>
		<desc>The 3rd chapter in this groundbreaking series brings 27 classic SNK characters together against Goenitz, the final boss.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof96.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof96.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof96.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42030" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof97.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '97</name>
		<desc>9 teams of 3 and 2 solo entries pump the number of selectable characters up to 29 in a battle to defeat the evil Orochi and those infected with his blood.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof97.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof97.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof97.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42031" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof98.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '98 - The Slugfest</name>
		<desc>A special edition of the KoF series taking place outside of the established storyline with a whopping 38 selectable KoF alumni.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof98.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof98.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof98.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42032" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kof99.fba</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '99 - Millennium Battle</name>
		<desc>Introducing the new 'striker' system! Each team is expanded to four characters, with a total of 30 selectable characters set on defeating Krizalid and his evil feather coat.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kof99.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kof99.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kof99.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37597" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kotm.fba</path>
		<name>King of the Monsters</name>
		<desc>King of the Monsters is a two player (or one player vs. computer) fighting game, in which the players take control of two gargantuan monsters (like Godzillas) and battle it out in different city locations.

The city gets gradually destroyed as the two creatures fight it out. The players can also interact with the scenery by picking up boats and such, to use as weapons against the other player.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kotm.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kotm.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kotm.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37598" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./kotm2.fba</path>
		<name>King of the Monsters 2 - The Next Thing</name>
		<desc>The object of King of the Monsters 2 is similar to its predecessor. Choose from three monsters which include a large lizard, a large robotic ape, and a huge mutant human. Then walk through each city, making sure to destroy everything in site, including planes, buildings, and other creatures. When smashed, some buildings reveal power-ups that make your character more powerful. At the end of each city, you go head-to-head with the boss creature. There are small stages in between where you fight a second monster for bonus points, or you fall from the sky and land underwater where you try to collect points and power-ups while falling.
</desc>
		<image>./boxart/kotm2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/kotm2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/kotm2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Takara</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42105" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./lastblad.fba</path>
		<name>The Last Blade</name>
		<desc>Japanese weapons-based fighter featuring beautiful artwork and sound. Twelve selectable characters and two end bosses.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/lastblad.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/lastblad.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/lastblad.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42106" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./lastbld2.fba</path>
		<name>The Last Blade 2</name>
		<desc>Much-acclaimed swordplay fighter with sixteen selectable characters and one end boss. Another SNK triumph!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/lastbld2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/lastbld2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/lastbld2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13976" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./lbowling.fba</path>
		<name>League Bowling</name>
		<desc>The lanes are crowded every night with Big Time Pin Slammin' action! You call the shots selecting a right or left handed bowler. Determine ball weight, and develop the skills of the pro's as you skillfully throw a variety of shots that you control. So pop some refreshments and settle into this indoor sport like you've never seen before!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/lbowling.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/lbowling.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/lbowling.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Bowling</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37601" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./legendos.fba</path>
		<name>Legend of Success Joe</name>
		<desc>Joe Yabuki is a little punk wandering the streets. He was spotted by a boxing coach retired from the circuit that sees him as a future champion and decides to manage him. Such is the plot of this boxing game on Neo Geo, adapted from the manga "Ashita no Joe" created by Tetsuya Chiba and Asao Takamori in the 70s.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/legendos.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/legendos.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/legendos.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wave Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Wave Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13957" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./lresort.fba</path>
		<name>Last Resort</name>
		<desc>Last Resort is a 1-2 player horizontal shooter game where you pilot a spacecraft across horizontally scrolling cityscapes and wastelands, while destroying hordes of enemy spacecraft, either metallic or organic, including huge mid- and end-level guardians. Getting power-up pods provide the craft with a movable drone which can be charged up and fired or locked into position and used as an extra gun or 'battering ram'/shield. A clone of R-Type (both one and two), but with much improved graphics and sound</desc>
		<image>./boxart/lresort.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/lresort.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/lresort.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13904" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./magdrop2.fba</path>
		<name>Magical Drop II</name>
		<desc>In Magical Drop II, you control a clown that can grab and throw balloons. You have to match three balloons of the same colour or more vertically to pop them and clear the screen. You can hold multiple balloons of the same colour at once and cause consecutive collisions. There are special balloons that cannot be removed that easily and power-ups that clear entire rows or provide additional help.

Depending of the originating country, there are different game modes:

1. Survival: Play as long as you can - an endless flow of balloons appears at a rapidly increasing speed while you move up levels.

2. Puzzle: You have a limited time to clear a fixed set of balloons before time runs out.

3. VS Mode: Fight the CPU or a fellow player in a direct split-screen duel. Each character has specific item balloons during gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/magdrop2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/magdrop2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/magdrop2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19961124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13883" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./magdrop3.fba</path>
		<name>Magical Drop III</name>
		<desc>This is the third installment in the puzzle frenzy series Magical Drop. In the game you control a clown who throws marbles up on the screen into the cluster of multi-colored marbles, rocks and crystals. The goal is to get three or more of the same color to remove marbles, but you can also grab more than one at the time to create long chain combos and gain better "special" blocks at the top of the screen.

You can play the game in single player modes or versus a friend in versus mode. In versus mode you get to pick your character, much like in a fighting game, each with their own counter attacks and abilities.

For the PSX version, the first Magical Drop was included on a separate disc.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/magdrop3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/magdrop3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/magdrop3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37602" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./maglord.fba</path>
		<name>Magician Lord</name>
		<desc>Magician Lord puts you in charge of Elta, a wizard who has the task of collecting eight books of wisdom from the clutches of Az Atorse, the god of destruction. By collecting the right power-ups along the way, you can transform into different characters, including the Rajin, Samurai, Waterman, Shinobi, Poseidon, and Dragon Warrior. Each character has different abilities. There are eight areas in the game, and each stage ends with you trying to defeat both a guardian and the end-of-area boss (which are basically Atorse's incarnations). One of the first games that demonstrated the graphical abilities of the Neo-Geo.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/maglord.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/maglord.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/maglord.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="78870" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./matrim.fba</path>
		<name>Matrimelee / Shin Gouketsuji Ichizoku Toukon</name>
		<desc>Matrimelee (c) 2002 Playmore.  Revived from the New Power Instinct series, the Goketsuji clan has appeared newly on the MVS Neo-Geo! In addition to the familiar 11 characters, individual fresh 4 join in the heated Head Decision Match. You will be overwhel</desc>
		<image>./boxart/matrim.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/matrim.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/matrim.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory / Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Noise Factory / Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="78920" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./miexchng.fba</path>
		<name>Money Puzzle Exchanger / Money Idol Exchanger</name>
		<desc>Money Puzzle Exchanger (c) 1997 Face.  Handling money has never been so much fun! This incredibly original puzzle game lets you take control of  hilariously designed characters in a cute Japanese superhero theme and boggle your mind with a puzzle system r</desc>
		<image>./boxart/miexchng.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/miexchng.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/miexchng.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FACE</developer>
		<publisher>FACE</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79010" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug.fba</path>
		<name>Metal Slug - Super Vehicle-001</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug - Super Vehicle-001 (c) 1996 Nazca.  A scrolling 'run-and-gun' platform game for one or two players, Metal Slug is a humorous parody of war and specifically of World War II and the Nazis.  The game features six enemy-packed levels, referred to </desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nazca</developer>
		<publisher>Nazca</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79011" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug2.fba</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 2 - Super Vehicle-001/II</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug 2 - Super Vehicle-001/II (c) 1998 SNK.  The heroes of Metal Slug, Marco and Tarma, are called into action once again to take on the might of General Morden and his armies in this, the first of several sequels to the superb 1996 original. This t</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79012" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug3.fba</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 3</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug 3 (c) 2000 SNK.  The heroes of the first 2 games return once more to do battle with the ever-present General Morden and his vast army. The third game of the series places a greater emphasis on defeating hulking boss characters than the 2 previo</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79013" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug4.fba</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 4</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug 4 (c) 2002 Playmore Corp.  The popular series of side-scrolling action games continues, introducing all-new characters into the plot. The world is now trembling under the fear of cyber terror, as the birth of a deadly new computer virus threate</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug4.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug4.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug4.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mega / Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>Mega / Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79001" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslug5.fba</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 5</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug 5 (c) 2003 SNK Playmore.  A research installation developing the next-generation of Metal Slugs is attacked by unknown forces and a disk containing Metal Slug secrets is stolen. Ordered to recover the disk, Marco and Tarma follow in hot pursuit</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslug5.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslug5.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslug5.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79014" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mslugx.fba</path>
		<name>Metal Slug X</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug X - Super Vehicle-001 (c) 1999 SNK.  Originally released to improve upon some of the problems the previous Metal Slug game ("Metal Slug 2 - Super Vehicle-001/II") had, most notably its notorious slowdown, this update also implemented several ch</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mslugx.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mslugx.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mslugx.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79043" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./mutnat.fba</path>
		<name>Mutation Nation</name>
		<desc>Mutation Nation (c) 1992 SNK [Shin Nihon Kikaku].  Two lone warriors with an array of special mutant powers attempt to restore order to this futuristic wasteland.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS Hardware Game ID : [Model NGM-014]  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 M</desc>
		<image>./boxart/mutnat.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/mutnat.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/mutnat.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 2.5D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="60786" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./nam1975.fba</path>
		<name>NAM-1975</name>
		<desc>NAM-1975 (c) 1990 SNK [Shin Nihon Kikaku].  One or two players take control of 2 machine-gun carrying Vietnam vets who must shoot their way through a number of sideways scrolling, Vietnam-themed levels. the players shoot into the screen and aiming is achi</desc>
		<image>./boxart/nam1975.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/nam1975.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/nam1975.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79066" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ncombat.fba</path>
		<name>Ninja Combat</name>
		<desc>Ninja Combat (c) 1990 Alpha Denshi.  The ninja castle must be invaded! After you defeat certain boss enemies, they become playable characters as well!  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : [Model NGM-009]  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CP</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ncombat.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ncombat.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ncombat.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi Co.</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Denshi Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79067" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ncommand.fba</path>
		<name>Ninja Commando</name>
		<desc>Ninja Commando (c) 1992 Alpha Denshi Co., Ltd.  3 ninjas are sent on a mission to stop a madman named Spider from trying to use a time machine to mess with history. The game is almost like a tongue-in-cheek reworking of "Time Soldiers", which Alpha Denshi</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ncommand.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ncommand.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ncommand.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi Co.</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Denshi Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79075" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./neobombe.fba</path>
		<name>Neo Bomberman</name>
		<desc>Neo Bomber Man (c) 05/1997 Hudson Soft.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0093  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels Scre</desc>
		<image>./boxart/neobombe.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/neobombe.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/neobombe.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="46957" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./neocup98.fba</path>
		<name>Neo Geo Cup '98: The Road To Victory</name>
		<desc>Neo Geo Cup'98 is a football simulation based on the World Cup 1998. This title is a new installment in the series Super Sidekicks and updates all data to focus on the event. In qualification phase or during games knockout, lead one of the 64 available teams to victory.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/neocup98.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/neocup98.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/neocup98.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980528T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79077" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./neodrift.fba</path>
		<name>Neo Drift Out - New Technology</name>
		<desc>Neo Drift Out - New Technology (c) 03/1996 Visco.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0213  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 p</desc>
		<image>./boxart/neodrift.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/neodrift.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/neodrift.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79078" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./neomrdo.fba</path>
		<name>Neo Mr. Do!</name>
		<desc>Neo Mr. Do! (c) 1996 Visco Corp.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0207  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 1 =&gt; [A] Attack enemy  - TRIVIA </desc>
		<image>./boxart/neomrdo.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/neomrdo.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/neomrdo.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79136" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ninjamas.fba</path>
		<name>Ninja Master's - haoh-ninpo-cho</name>
		<desc>Ninja Master's Haoh Ninpou-chou (c) 1996 SNK  Criminally overlooked and combo-friendly medieval Japanese fighter with great animation. Ten selectable characters and two end bosses.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 217  Main CPU : 68000 (</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ninjamas.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ninjamas.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ninjamas.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK / SNK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79139" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./nitd.fba</path>
		<name>Nightmare in the Dark</name>
		<desc>Nightmare in the Dark (c) 2000 Eleven / Gavaking.  A peaceful (yet creepy looking!) gravekeeper embarks on a night-shift battle against zombies &amp; other night dwellers in order to put an end to the grave robbing mystery before the local villagers panic! Fe</desc>
		<image>./boxart/nitd.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/nitd.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/nitd.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eleven / Gavaking</developer>
		<publisher>Eleven / Gavaking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79116" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./overtop.fba</path>
		<name>Over Top</name>
		<desc>Over Top (c) 1996 ADK.  You drive different vehicles in this 3D-like 2D game. The backgrounds are quiet nicely done. The task is to finish every race before certain time. There are many hidden shortcuts in this game.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardwa</desc>
		<image>./boxart/overtop.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/overtop.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/overtop.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79180" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./panicbom.fba</path>
		<name>Panic Bomber</name>
		<desc>Panic Bomber - Bomber Man (c) 1995 Eighting.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0073  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels</desc>
		<image>./boxart/panicbom.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/panicbom.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/panicbom.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting / Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Eighting / Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79202" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pbobbl2n.fba</path>
		<name>Puzzle Bobble 2 / Bust-A-Move Again</name>
		<desc>Puzzle Bobble 2 (c) 1999 Taito Corp.  MVS re-release. For more information about the game itself, please see the original "Puzzle Bobble 2" (Taito F3 version) entry.  - TECHNICAL -  Game ID : 0248  - TRIVIA -  This game is known in US as "Bust-A-Move Agai</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pbobbl2n.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pbobbl2n.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pbobbl2n.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito (SNK license)</developer>
		<publisher>Taito (SNK license)</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43539" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pbobblen.fba</path>
		<name>Puzzle Bobble</name>
		<desc>The first in the hugely successful puzzle series from Taito, Puzzle Bobble is a game for 1 or 2 players in which the aim is to clear each play area of the colored bubbles that litter it. This is achieved by firing bubbl</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pbobblen.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pbobblen.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pbobblen.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Unknown</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79254" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pgoal.fba</path>
		<name>Pleasure Goal / Futsal - 5 on 5 Mini Soccer</name>
		<desc>Pleasure Goal - 5 on 5 Mini Soccer (c) 1996 Saurus.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0219  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pgoal.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pgoal.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pgoal.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42429" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pnyaa.fba</path>
		<name>Pochi and Nyaa</name>
		<desc>Pochi to Nyaa is a cutesy puzzle game where the objective is to match the colored invaders in chains much in the vein of the Sega game "Puyo Puyo Fever". Pochi to Nyaa features three different modes of play: story mode, vs. c</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pnyaa.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pnyaa.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pnyaa.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aiky</developer>
		<publisher>Aiky / Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42464" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./popbounc.fba</path>
		<name>Pop 'n Bounce</name>
		<desc>Pop 'n Bounce (c) 1997 Video System.  A breakout-style game.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0237  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : </desc>
		<image>./boxart/popbounc.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/popbounc.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/popbounc.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Videosystem</developer>
		<publisher>Video System Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42502" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./preisle2.fba</path>
		<name>Prehistoric Isle 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to "Prehistoric Isle in 1930", release more that 10 years after the first one.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/preisle2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/preisle2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/preisle2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Yumekobo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42523" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pspikes2.fba</path>
		<name>Power Spikes II</name>
		<desc>Power Spikes II (c) 1994 Video System.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0068  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 2 =&gt; [A] At service Toss/H</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pspikes2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pspikes2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pspikes2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Video System Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42549" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./pulstar.fba</path>
		<name>Pulstar</name>
		<desc>An accomplished and graphically superb sideways scrolling shoot-em-up that borrows many of its visual and gameplay elements from all three games in Irem's legendary "R-Type" series; including the Beam weapon and R-type's infamo</desc>
		<image>./boxart/pulstar.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/pulstar.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/pulstar.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Aicom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="94165" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./puzzldpr.fba</path>
		<name>Puzzle De Pon! R!</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/puzzldpr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/puzzldpr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/puzzldpr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="42564" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./puzzledp.fba</path>
		<name>Puzzle De Pon!</name>
		<desc>Drop the target plate before time runs out to clear each stage. To finish the game, clear 39 different stages... </desc>
		<image>./boxart/puzzledp.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/puzzledp.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/puzzledp.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Taito (Visco license)</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79422" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ragnagrd.fba</path>
		<name>Ragnagard / Shin-Oh-Ken</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/ragnagrd.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ragnagrd.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ragnagrd.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="42704" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./rbff1.fba</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury</name>
		<desc>16 characters, some old and some new, breathe new life into the Fatal Fury series.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/rbff1.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/rbff1.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/rbff1.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42705" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./rbff2.fba</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury 2 - The Newcomers</name>
		<desc>23 of the finest South Town fighters in the 7th installment of this SNK game.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/rbff2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/rbff2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/rbff2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42706" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./rbffspec.fba</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury Special</name>
		<desc>'Hey, how's it goin', dude?' More old Fatal favorites return to the bout and bring the total of selectable fighters to 19.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/rbffspec.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/rbffspec.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/rbffspec.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42762" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ridhero.fba</path>
		<name>Riding Hero</name>
		<desc>A Hot Battle Awaits You On The Way To The W.G.P Racing Title! After getting the 'International A License', a young racer battles his way to the Suzuka 8 Hour Race. Featuring 3 ways to play! W.G.P mode, RPG mode or Multi Play mod</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ridhero.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ridhero.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ridhero.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42790" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./roboarmy.fba</path>
		<name>Robo Army</name>
		<desc>Two robotic soldiers attempt to stop the robots and their master from enslaving the human race.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/roboarmy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/roboarmy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/roboarmy.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42819" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./rotd.fba</path>
		<name>Rage of the Dragons</name>
		<desc>Rage of the Dragons is an original fighting game with 14 selectable fighters plus Abubo (sub-boss, hidden character) and Johann (final boss).</desc>
		<image>./boxart/rotd.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/rotd.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/rotd.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Evoga</developer>
		<publisher>Evoga / Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42861" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./s1945p.fba</path>
		<name>Strikers 1945 Plus</name>
		<desc>Strikers 1945 Plus was a remake of Strikers 1945 II for the Neo Geo platform. Plus was the only game in the series with a horizonal monitor configuration.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/s1945p.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/s1945p.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/s1945p.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Psikyo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="79411" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsh5sp.fba</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown V Special</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsh5sp.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsh5sp.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsh5sp.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20040000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yuki Enterprise / SNK Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>Yuki Enterprise / SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="79412" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho.fba</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown / Samurai Spirits</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsho.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="79413" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho2.fba</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown II / Shin Samurai Spirits - Haohma</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsho2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="79414" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho3.fba</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown III / Samurai Spirits - Zankurou M</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsho3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="79415" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho4.fba</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown IV - Amakusa's Revenge / Samurai S</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/samsho4.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho4.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho4.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="42885" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./samsho5.fba</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown V</name>
		<desc>A 5th episode of the Samurai Shodown saga on Neo-Geo with 24 selectable characters plus Poppy (secret character) plus 3 bosses (Sankuro the mid-boss, Yumeji the sub-boss and the general Gaoh as final boss).</desc>
		<image>./boxart/samsho5.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/samsho5.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/samsho5.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yuki Enterprise</developer>
		<publisher>Yuki Enterprise / SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42898" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./savagere.fba</path>
		<name>Savage Reign</name>
		<desc>10 fighters, each brandishing a weapon, fight to have a crack at the Real King Leo. There are 2 planes of action to switch from and in some cases the player can use elements of the background as weapons.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/savagere.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/savagere.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/savagere.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43227" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sdodgeb.fba</path>
		<name>Super Dodge Ball</name>
		<desc>The object is to hit your opponent's player with the ball while avoiding being hit. Once a player has been hit three times, that player is out of the game. The game is won by knocking all the opposing players out of the game.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sdodgeb.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sdodgeb.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sdodgeb.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Leland Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42966" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sengoku.fba</path>
		<name>Sengoku</name>
		<desc>Two warriors, endowed with spiritual gifts, fight to stop the resurrection of the Mad Shogun. Lots of very interesting enemies and beautiful scenery. The player also has the ability to morph into different fighte</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sengoku.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sengoku.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sengoku.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42967" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sengoku2.fba</path>
		<name>Sengoku 2</name>
		<desc>The Mad Shogun rises again, this time taking over various periods in the time stream. Now you're permanently armed with a sword and must save different eras from the wrath of the Mad Shogun!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sengoku2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sengoku2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sengoku2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="42968" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sengoku3.fba</path>
		<name>Sengoku 3</name>
		<desc>Taking quite a different approach than the previous 2 Sengoku games, the 3rd in the series introduces 4 characters and a new chain combo system. 2 bosses, when defeated, can also be selected for battle for the final 2 stages.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sengoku3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sengoku3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sengoku3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Noise Factory / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43049" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./shocktr2.fba</path>
		<name>Shock Troopers - 2nd Squad</name>
		<desc>More of an update than a full-blown sequel, Shock Troopers - 2nd Squad picks up where the first game - released a year earlier - left off. Once again, one or two players face the might of a terrorist army who are </desc>
		<image>./boxart/shocktr2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/shocktr2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/shocktr2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43050" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./shocktro.fba</path>
		<name>Shock Troopers</name>
		<desc>TheBigL1 rates this game: 5/5This overhead run n' gun shooter has eight different characters you can play as, who all have different weapons and movement speed.
Tapping the A button lets you sweep your shots with your guns, and you can hold the button to strafe. If you press B you'll do a rolling dodge, which you can use to evade enemy bullets. You press C to use your secondary weapon, which is very strong but has limited ammo. Each character has a different default gun and secondary weapon.
Enemy attacks will deplete your health gauge, and if it drops to zero then you'll need to put in another credit to keep going. You can find food and first-aid kits to heal yourself, and before starting each level you get some health back.
Special guns are found throughout the levels, and can be used until they run out of ammo or you get another gun. There are also pickups to replenish your secondary weapon, and attacking enemies in close-range will make them drop point bonuses.
When starting the game you can use one character or a team of three. If you choose a team of three, you can press D during play to switch between them.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/shocktro.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/shocktro.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/shocktro.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43163" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./socbrawl.fba</path>
		<name>Soccer Brawl</name>
		<desc>Soccer Brawl (c) 1992 SNK.  A futuristic soccer game.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID: [Model NGM-031]  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  [SNK MVS Neo-Geo Controls] 2 players - 4 buttons</desc>
		<image>./boxart/socbrawl.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/socbrawl.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/socbrawl.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37641" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sonicwi2.fba</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters 2</name>
		<desc>Aero Fighters 2 is a vertically-scrolling shooter in the same vein as 1942 and similar games. It supports up to two players and  has 8 different aircraft to choose from, each equipped with unique primary and secondary weapons. Power-ups upgrade the look, power, size and shape of the shots. Bombs activate a special power that usually wipes off the enemies on the screen. The game has a total of 10 stages (Japan, Brazil, Atlantic, U.S.A., France, Australia, Himalayas, Mexico, Hawaii and Space), all of them with a boss battle.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sonicwi2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sonicwi2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sonicwi2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="37642" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./sonicwi3.fba</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters 3</name>
		<desc>Aero Fighters 3 is a vertically-scrolling shooter in the same vein as 1942 and similar games. It supports up to two players and  has 10 different aircraft to choose from, each equipped with unique primary and secondary weapons. Power-ups upgrade the look, power, size and shape of the shots. Bombs activate a special power that usually wipes off the enemies on the screen. The game has a total of 8 stages placed on several countries (Japan, Germany, Libya, Egypt, Pacific, U.S.A., England, France, Panama, Thailand, Ukraine, Atlantic and Space), all of them with a boss battle.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/sonicwi3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/sonicwi3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/sonicwi3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19951117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43251" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./spinmast.fba</path>
		<name>Spin Master</name>
		<desc>Johnny &amp; Tom, two treasure seekers must save their friend Mary from the evil Mad Doctor and his army of goofy-dressed henchmen, as well as gather the map pieces in order to find the biggest treasure in the world at the</desc>
		<image>./boxart/spinmast.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/spinmast.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/spinmast.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43312" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ssideki.fba</path>
		<name>Super Sidekicks</name>
		<desc>Super Sidekicks (c) 1992 SNK.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 052  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 2 =&gt; Offense &gt; [A] Long kick/Shoot, </desc>
		<image>./boxart/ssideki.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ssideki.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ssideki.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43313" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ssideki2.fba</path>
		<name>Super Sidekicks 2 - The World Championship</name>
		<desc>Super Sidekicks 2 - The World Championship (c) 1994 SNK.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 061  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 3 =&gt; Atta</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ssideki2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ssideki2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ssideki2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43314" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ssideki3.fba</path>
		<name>Super Sidekicks 3 - The Next Glory</name>
		<desc>Super Sidekicks is the 3rd game in the famous Super Sidekicks series of soccer games. Featuring 6 competition modes for 64 world wide teams. Utilizes Digitized Trace Animation and 3-D camera angled shots f</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ssideki3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ssideki3.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ssideki3.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43315" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./ssideki4.fba</path>
		<name>The Ultimate 11 - The SNK Football Championship</name>
		<desc>The Ultimate 11 - SNK Football Championship (c) 1996 SNK.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 215  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz)a Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Players : 2 Control : 8-way joystick Buttons : 3 =&gt; At</desc>
		<image>./boxart/ssideki4.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ssideki4.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ssideki4.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43342" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./stakwin.fba</path>
		<name>Stakes Winner</name>
		<desc>Stakes Winner (c) 1995 Saurus.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0088  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels Screen refres</desc>
		<image>./boxart/stakwin.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/stakwin.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/stakwin.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43343" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./stakwin2.fba</path>
		<name>Stakes Winner 2</name>
		<desc>Stakes Winner 2 (c) 1996 Saurus.  - TECHNICAL -  SNK Neo-Geo MVS hardware Game ID : 0227  Main CPU : 68000 (@ 12 Mhz) Sound CPU : Z80 (@ 4 Mhz) Sound Chips : YM2610 (@ 8 Mhz)  Screen orientation : Horizontal Video resolution : 320 x 224 pixels Screen refr</desc>
		<image>./boxart/stakwin2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/stakwin2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/stakwin2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Saurus</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43394" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./strhoop.fba</path>
		<name>Street Hoop</name>
		<desc>A basketball game from the streets. Choose from one of ten countries and compete in three-on-three slamdunkin' action.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/strhoop.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/strhoop.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/strhoop.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43433" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./superspy.fba</path>
		<name>The Super Spy</name>
		<desc>Infiltrate terrorist hideouts and beat up the bad guys in this gender-bending (but still good) first-person beat-em-up with RPG elements.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/superspy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/superspy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/superspy.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43466" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./svc.fba</path>
		<name>SVC Chaos : SNK vs. Capcom</name>
		<desc>A one-on-one fighting game - the collaboration between Capcom and SNK - pits seventeen well-known SNK combatants against seventeen of Capcom's most famous game characters.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/svc.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/svc.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/svc.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43674" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./tophuntr.fba</path>
		<name>Top Hunter - Roddy &amp; Cathy</name>
		<desc>An unique action platform game that feature Roddy &amp; Cathy, 2 powerful bounty hunters that are determined to wipe out the space pirate army! Features excellent 2-D graphics &amp; plenty of secrets to find!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/tophuntr.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/tophuntr.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/tophuntr.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43707" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./tpgolf.fba</path>
		<name>Top Player's Golf</name>
		<desc />
		<image>./boxart/tpgolf.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/tpgolf.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/tpgolf.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43713" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./trally.fba</path>
		<name>Thrash Rally</name>
		<desc>Thrash Rally is a top-down perspective rally racing game for one or two players. Each race begins with players asked to choose a vehicle in which to race, with each offering a different balance between handling, accele</desc>
		<image>./boxart/trally.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/trally.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/trally.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Denshi Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43780" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./turfmast.fba</path>
		<name>Neo Turf Masters</name>
		<desc>An absolutely superb arcade golf game in which one or two players choose from a selection of six different golfers, each possessing different strengths and weaknesses. Four eighteen-hole golf courses are available: German</desc>
		<image>./boxart/turfmast.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/turfmast.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/turfmast.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nazca</developer>
		<publisher>Nazca</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43808" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./twinspri.fba</path>
		<name>Twinkle Star Sprites</name>
		<desc>Competitive shooter with flavors of Galaga, Fighting Games, and Sailor Moon.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/twinspri.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/twinspri.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/twinspri.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ADK / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43813" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./tws96.fba</path>
		<name>Tecmo World Soccer '96</name>
		<desc>An excellent soccer game featuring great graphics, tons of voiceovers and some of the world's best football nations.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/tws96.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/tws96.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/tws96.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="43958" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./viewpoin.fba</path>
		<name>Viewpoint</name>
		<desc>Viewpoint is an isometric shooter developed by Sammy and published by SNK for release on various platforms.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/viewpoin.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/viewpoin.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/viewpoin.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sammy Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy / Aicom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Diagonal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44022" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wakuwak7.fba</path>
		<name>Waku Waku 7</name>
		<desc>Sunsoft's second 2D fighter for the NeoGeo system.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wakuwak7.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wakuwak7.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wakuwak7.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44061" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wh1.fba</path>
		<name>World Heroes</name>
		<desc>8 heroes from different time periods compete to thwart Geegus, the evil alien end boss! Includes an extremely fun and unique death match mode!</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wh1.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wh1.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wh1.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Denshi</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Denshi Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44062" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wh2.fba</path>
		<name>World Heroes 2</name>
		<desc>14 characters and 2 end bosses do battle in normal or death match modes.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wh2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wh2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wh2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44063" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wh2j.fba</path>
		<name>World Heroes 2 Jet</name>
		<desc>This update of World Heroes 2 introduces two new characters, Ryofu and Jack and 2 new modes of play - the Tournament and the Forging of Warriors.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wh2j.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wh2j.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wh2j.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ADK / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44069" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./whp.fba</path>
		<name>World Heroes Perfect</name>
		<desc>A new button layout for the final game in the series greets the 16 fighters, 1 hidden fighter and 2 end bosses.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/whp.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/whp.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/whp.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ADK / SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44100" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./wjammers.fba</path>
		<name>Windjammers</name>
		<desc>Windjammers (also known as Flying Power Disc in Japan) is a fast pace, sport arcade game released by Data East on the Neo Geo arcade system in 1994 and later on the Wii Virtual Console in Japan on June 22, 2010. Following the bankruptcy of Data East, the intellectual rights for this game were acquired by Paon</desc>
		<image>./boxart/wjammers.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/wjammers.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/wjammers.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44196" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./zedblade.fba</path>
		<name>Zed Blade</name>
		<desc>Zed Blade is a sideways scrolling shoot-em-up for one or two players. Players can chose from three different ships, each with varying speeds.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/zedblade.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/zedblade.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/zedblade.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NMK</developer>
		<publisher>NMK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="44223" source="ScreenScraper">
		<path>./zupapa.fba</path>
		<name>Zupapa!</name>
		<desc>Is a 2001 release of SNK for MVS. It's pretty much a puzzler / screen-cleaning game with bright and colourful optics and simple gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/zupapa.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/zupapa.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/zupapa.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./neogeo.zip</path>
		<name>Neo-Geo</name>
		<image>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/neogeo/boxart/neogeo.png</image>
		<video>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/neogeo/snap/neogeo.mp4</video>
		<marquee>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/neogeo/wheel/neogeo.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players />
		<hidden>true</hidden>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3countb.zip</path>
		<name>3 Count Bout</name>
		<desc>3 Count Bout is a one-on-one fighting game. Choose from ten wrestlers who have their own power attacks. There are ten rounds in the game, and each one of them has you fighting other wrestlers that are much tougher than the previous ones. You defeat each one by biting, kicking, and performing other moves to the point where their damage meter is empty. But just because it is empty doesn't mean that you win. You have to pin him for the infamous-three count. Also features competitive play and tag match battles.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/3countb.png</image>
		<video>./snap/3countb.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/3countb.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930000T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>UPL</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20180313T093229</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
